色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Gareki-kun.
We've been given permission.
Let's go in.
Come on, what's Nai-chan's condition?!
Tell me, Gramps!
Gareki-kun, keep down.
Huh?
Hold your tongue!
Moron, you're being too loud around the patient!
Score 3
Phantom Picnic
There are no injuries on his body,
but for a moment there was a strong disturbance in his brain waves.
Now he has temporarily lost consciousness.
You should probably investigate the reason behind this at the Research Tower.
I see...
Then, I shall not waste any more time and will take my leave immediately.
Take that fool over there with you!
Feel free to use him for human experimentation.
Doc, when will he regain consciousness?
I'm responsible...
I was entrusted to look after him and yet...
His condition is stable, so I think he should wake up soon.
Tsukumo, you should learn to relax more.
You only need to shoulder your own responsibilities.
I'll take my leave now!
Please, take care of Nai-kun!
Hmm?
Ma~ Ma~ Ma~ Ma~
He was in so much pain before,
and yet you say there's nothing wrong with him.
You're not some kind of quack, are you?
You're such a foul-mouthed kid.
Worried about your friend?
We just happened to be together.
It's ridiculous to assume that we're friends.
Encounters happen both through coincidence and through the course of nature.
If trust grows from within here,
you'll be friends forever.
Hey! Where are you going?
Supper! I'm going for supper!
Make sure you look after him!
What?!
Nai.
Why aren't you devoting all your attention to finding me?
Is there someone by your side?
Karoku!
Where are you?
What kind of person is he?
Oh, Gareki...
To be able to make friends with someone...
that's my boy.
But...  let's say goodbye to that person.
Huh?
But... why?
Well, because I don't want you to feel sad.
You should tell him, "Gareki, I don't need you!"
But I... Gareki is...
You wouldn't want him to be dragged into the scary things happening around you,
and be broken, would you?
Ga–
You startled me.
How are you feeling?
If there's anything you want me to do, I'll hear you out this time.
Ga–
You wouldn't want him to be broken, would you?
Gareki, I don't need you.
What?
Gareki, I don't...
Tell me... what do you mean by that?
Huh?
Gareki's sca–
I'm scary? You're saying this after all we've been through?
Ga–
Gareki!
What's up with that?
Are you telling me that you'll give me what I want, so I should just go away?
Since you're already acquainted with Circus...
Sorry, but I hate people who act innocent but are actually opportunists.
That hurt...
Geez... Gramps, you're no ordinary old man,
so go easy on me– Huh?
What?
Huh? What?
Gareki-kun?
Tell that bearded old geezer that the damn brat is awake!
I get it... so just calm down.
All right? Okay?
Wai–
Gareki-kun!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Where does it hurt?
Um... what should I do?
Tsukumo-chan... huh?
Off-limits! Off-limits! Off-limits!
Yogi?
What's the matter?
Yogi!
What...?
I got it.
Tsukumo, I'll leave it to you.
So? You didn't come here for supper, did you?
About that boy's body...
What's wrong with Nai's body?
Are there any significant problems with it?
Well... to put it simply,
that boy isn't human.
He's an animal.
It's natural that you'd feel shocked–
What a bad joke... oh no it's nothing.
I heard that!
Here! Take a look at this!
This is the true form of that boy!
Say what?
No way...
I've come to this conclusion based on cellular tissue samples extracted from his body.
Its scientific name is "Niji."
Its species can only be found in the Niji Forest, which contains a unique ecosystem.
It's an extremely rare animal.
I can't believe it...
Wait, wait a second!
But if what Doc says is true...
Um... well...
Does he expect me to believe that Nai's not actually human...
That based on the data, he's an animal...
There's no way I can simply accept all this!
Since meeting members of Circus,
I've learned that there are humans who become monsters.
Though it's true that Nai's actions always tend to be a bit strange...
Does this mean that up until now...
I'm Gareki.
Who are you?
Nai!
Thanks.
Come again?
You saved me again!
Gareki, I don't need you!
Don't need you! Don't need you!
I've been such a fool?!
I've talked to the Research Tower.
Bring him there tomorrow.
Urp... I'm going to see Akari-sensei?
Oh... that reminds me, about Nai-chan's bracelet,
you're not going to take it from him?
I'm just trying to see if it responds to that boy.
Huh?
But wouldn't the bracelet only respond to its owner?
Nai-chan said it was left by that guy, Karoku.
What if he's lying?
No way...
If he's a member of Kafka, it would be possible, right?
Well...
I was surprised to find out about his body...
but I'm sure he's a good boy!
Wai– What are you laughing about?
Oh nothing...
That's why I assigned you to him.
You're probably thinking that I'll definitely go easy on him...
Don't think too much about it.
All these little safeguards are just a precaution.
Sit.
I should calm down.
He's just a boy... no, just an animal.
No matter how you look at it, he looks like a human...
And now they're saying that he's an animal?
That just makes me even more embarrassed!
I'll look like a fool if I get angry.
In fact, you've always asked me for help, so what's this about me being scary?!
Talk to me!
You're not scary!
What?
I was told that you would be broken... by Karoku.
Karoku?
Never mind.
Go on.
If I don't want you getting dragged into the scary things, and being broken...
Karoku said I should say goodbye.
He said it would be better if I told you that I didn't need you.
How can you speak to a person you can't even find?
Just now...
Before I woke up...
He's trying to tell me... that it happened in a dream?
Damn animal!
He said I should say goodbye to avoid you being broken.
He said it would be better if I said I didn't need you.
Now that I think about it, what a "great" personality that guy has.
He seems like a hypocrite...
I'll ask again. What's your relationship with Karoku?
Karoku's always been with me–
You've already said that!
So, how long have you been so close?
As long as I remember...
Roughly when?
He doesn't know?
Well then, did you tell Karoku about me?
I told him I was with you...
Is that all?
Then, why did Karoku try to keep me away from him?
Those words even seem to have malicious intent.
Also if he can communicate, why did he leave this boy alone?
In fact, how is he communicating.
If that's how he sets off communication, he really does have some "great" taste.
Well, my impression of you has changed quite a bit, Karoku.
On top of that, he's picking a fight with me...
Gareki?
First of all; I'm sorry, I heard you wrong.
I don't really dislike you.
Moreover,
I have no intention of being broken.
I've also taken interest in meeting Karoku
Sure.
From now on, you will be examined in the Research Tower.
If it's about Nai being an animal and not being human,
he won't be treated like a lab animal, will he?
Doc will go with you.
If they try to use Nai for any experiments, scream and beg him to help.
What kind of advice is that?
Yogi,
I will leave these two in your care.
Yes, but what about Hirato-san and Tsukumo-chan?
We're being called to Round Table Z?
Why didn't they take them to the Research Tower right away?
I think their reason for being cautious is to find out who the real owner of that bracelet is.
Their methods are messed up.
We'll find out when we get there.
Fly... high!
Yahooo!
Hey, Tsukumo-senpai.
Long time no see.
Did you gain a little weight?
Now now.
Those companies that cooperate with Kafka are not only good at hiding their association,
but the number of Varuga which had decreased at one point are starting to increase again.
They stole the evolution research we had sealed, and are using it as we speak.
We have to protect many lives from the mistakes of our former comrades.
And, Hirato.
About the boy that Doc has reported on...
There is nothing physically wrong with you, including your blood cells.
Everything is fine, except for your personality.
Then, I'll take these off.
Thank you for your trouble.
We have a room ready for you. Get some rest.
Come to think of it, where is Yogi?
I don't know.
He left before I noticed.
Well, I thought he was already getting prodded, he's such a pain in the neck.
No one else is around.
He's not around...
What are you doing?
What! Ah, Akari-sensei.
Are you changing your bandage every day?
The reaction can be terrifying, if you don't take it seriously.
Okay.
If you forget it again, treatment would not be as easy as the last time.
Well, I.. I.. will try my best.
It looks a lot like where I lived with Karoku.
Where?
Right there.
What was the place Gareki lived like?
It was a filthy dump.
When you're in a dirty place with dirty people, you don't forget the anger towards them.
It's okay.
I haven't forgotten
But...
Since I met you, I feel like I only see pure things.
Seeing so many things and learning how to think purely,
then growing up and forgetting the anger.
I don't want to be the only one who is comfortable.
But if, unconsciously, I wanted to escape...
If being with Nai prevents me from running away.
Should I go back?
Gareki.
If you can see pure things as pure,
that means Gareki's eyes are pure too!
Gareki, what's wrong?
It's fine.
I was pretty pissed off.
I am still filthy.
Gareki...
His internal body formation is quite similar to a Varuga,
but Nai is a new species formed from the miraculous...
co-existence and amalgamation of human and Niji cells.
The one who created Nai is undoubtedly a genius.
Then, dissect him immediately to unravel the details.
Tsukumo,
sit down.
I cannot follow that order.
What?
If we dissect him, we will lose an enormous amount of invaluable data.
I cannot accept throwing away such a masterpiece without any consideration.
They are from Doc.
Hooray!
Treating you like a pet...
Aren't you just being used?
That's not true!
Nai-chan offered to come with us of his own accord.
Niji Forest?
The place we think you were living.
We may find something out if we go there.
About both Nai-chan and Karoku-san.
If you don't wish to cooperate with us and would rather leave instead,
I'll make sure I "sleep soundly" tonight.
I will go.
I want to truly understand what Karoku meant.
I also want to have a better understanding of what everyone is thinking.
You're such a good boy, Nai-chan.
You're annoying.
Hurry up and take off already!
Then, we'll be blasting off toward Niji Forest!
Blast off? For what?
U-Um...
Sorry, well, we're taking off.
Niji Forest is a peculiar area where unnatural rainbows and mirages occur.
Its unique ecological electromagnetic waves influence the optical nerve.
This electromagnetic wave causes all electronic devices to malfunction.
So, this leads to a search that can only depend on hearing.
So that's why Nai, being an animal from that place, is so sensitive to sound...
It's been about an hour.
He is walking without hesitation, where there is no distinct trail.
Is that a mirage?
Let's go.
Only the house is burnt.
The destruction wasn't due to natural causes.
Check it out.
Yes.
It was seen in the aerial photos of the forest.
It would have been impossible to reach without Nai.
Some unnatural being came to erase the evidence.
Nai-chan.
Cheer up.
There is another place I stayed for a long time.
Where is it?
Here.
A cave?
Get down!
Huh?
Varuga?!
Are you after Nai-chan again?
I'm actually scared of fighting since failure isn't an option.
But I will fight if I need to fight!
Nai!
Damn it!
Gareki-kun!
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Hey, what do they mean when they say you're an animal?
Well...
You seem human in every way.
Don't tell me, maybe you can transform?
Huh?
Go ahead and transform. I'm interested. Do it now!
What on earth do you mean by "transform"?!
Score 4
Evening Swallow