Score 13
Karneval
Be my reason
Everything...
subete ga ima
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
By your side...
Be my reason
Starts moving now
kimi no soba de
Be my power, future
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
kanjou no namae nante
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
There'll be no end to it
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
honnou de kikiwakeru
(Trust)
I follow you around
tsukimatou
(Trash)
It's over there
soko ni aru
Both the light and darkness
hikari mo yami mo
tsunagari dasu
They begin to connect
Like puzzle pieces
piisu no you ni
Because there is a reason
riyuu ga aru kara
Whether it happened by chance or by design
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
The temperature of my heart
kokoro no ondo ga
Rises little by little
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
I'm just being myself
hontou no jibun no mama de
I want to tell you
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
Be my reason
Everything...
subete ga ima
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
By your side...
Be my reason
By your side
kimi no soba de
Be my power, future
When things unfold naturally
arifureta tenkai nara
I should just set my mind at ease
anshin te wake ja nai daro
Always giving my all to anything
kurikaesu kakugo no rensa
Can also make me stronger
tsuyoku mo nareru sa
(Cloud)
Don't turn away
sorasazu ni
(Crash)
Deceive yourself no longer
mou nani mo gomakasanaide
Just accept it
uketorun da
It fits you perfectly
jibun ni niau
A future that will dazzle
mabushii mirai wo
The brightness beyond your false pride
bukiyou na puraido sono saki no buraito
Show the way with your smile
mitsuketai egao wo terashite
We will surely
bokura wa kanarazu
Reach the place where you are
soko ni tadoritsuku yo
Don't do it on a whim, nor to ease your mind
kimagure ja nai kiyasume mo nai
sei ippai no ima wo hashire
Right now, just run with all your might
As you feel something from
kasanari au bekutoru ni
Our fates which overlap
imi wo kanjinagara
Be my reason
By your side
kimi no soba de
Be my power, future