Yotaka!
Yogi, stand back.
色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Score 6
Wings of Morning Light
What a miserable sight you are.
Such sloppy work, and letting your blood  be spilled.
You are the disgrace of Circus.
Kiichi.
Why is someone from the First Ship here...
Just because the enemy was an acquaintance of someone you know,
you hesitated to put him to rest and instead had the tables turned on you.
You're so soft that it makes me sick.
How long have you been here?
Having someone like you share the same rank as an elite like me, Kiichi, is so annoying.
Oh, good job being a decoy.
Yotaka...
Yogi is hurt.
Tsubame-chan is crying.
Gareki-kun, well…
You look badly hurt.
Are you okay?
Yeah, thanks for asking.
Gareki isn't hurt badly.
He's not crying, but I think he's just holding it back.
I'm not hurt either, yet I feel a tightness in my chest.
It's like feeling sad...
Why do I feel this way?
And when I think of that man, I feel sick.
I get a cold feeling right here and it hurts.
A coward who never comes out to act in
person but enjoys tormenting the weak,
as noted on the First Ship's wanted list.
When your pet grew unexpectedly strong and hurt Yogi,
did you get carried away and miss the chance to escape?
It’s fun to torment others, isn't it?
Go!
Your girls are great.
You control them well.
Capture completed, huh?
I deeply appreciate your cooperation, Second Ship Captain, Hirato-dono.
You're so full of nonsense.
Return.
That's so unkind, I was just thanking you.
Yogi-san, are you with
that person who killed Yotaka?
Yeah.
Wait, Tsubame, they are members of Circus.
Circus?
You know about Circus, don’t you?
The elite group of people who hunt down criminals.
I happened to get involved with these people,
and learned that there are monsters called Varuga.
They killed Tsubaki and turned Yotaka into that.
Gareki-kun, I will tell her the rest.
The organization that’s creating Varuga
is called Kafka by the government.
There are two distinct kinds of Varuga.
One kind is created by Kafka
itself by repeated cell fusion.
And the other kind transforms due to damage to their
cells caused by Varuga blood or body fluid.
They're originally victims, just like Yotaka-kun.
The drug Yotaka-kun was forced to take was
probably implanted with Varuga cells.
The drug.
Varuga have an extremely fast cell renewal cycle.
Even if they get badly hurt, they'll recover in a few days.
In order to support that rapid metabolic system,
they devour others and integrate the cells of their victims into themselves.
Circus' mission is to eliminate all Varugas,
put them to rest, and to annihilate Kafka.
Our role is to end the lives of those...
who were made to undergo twisted
evolution based on the desires of others,
and set them free from all their chains.
I'm sorry. "Set them free" is too nice a way to say it.
That's what we were told,
but in the end,
we're just killing people who turned into Varuga...
because we can't return them to how they were before.
Then...
kill me.
You...
Kill me too.
What are you talking about!
You're not a Varuga!
I was taking that drug for a while too.
I may transform some day.
Tsubame-chan.
Also, Yotaka isn't here anymore!
I don’t want to be alone.
I don't like that. I'm scared of being alone.
Tsubaki-oneechan died, and Grandpa who
was in the hospital forgot all about me.
And now, Yotaka has died too.
Even so, your grandfather is still alive!
Didn't the two of you work really hard in order to pay the hospital fees?!
The money we earned wasn't nearly enough.
But apparently, Grandpa's old friend had been paying part of the fees.
That's what the nurse secretly told me.
So he'll be fine even if I'm gone.
I just want to disappear...
Tsubame...
Tsubame-chan is crying.
Drip, drop.
It's almost as if she's sinking.
Kii-chan, did you find anything over there?
There are lots of research materials,
but nothing indicates his connection with Kafka.
Sheesh, they really have their bases covered.
I didn't think they would leave any evidence from the beginning.
But I can't help but admire them for the extreme care they take.
Even if they're the enemy,
I cannot help but praise them.
Jiki-kun, what are you thinking, admiring the enemy?
Well, the only thing left to do
is to ask him directly, isn't it?
What a sorry sight you are.
You sound just like Akari-chan.
That's not the way you should address
someone who's 6 years older than you.
Show him respect and call him "sensei."
Okay, okay.
Oh right, speaking of Akari-sensei, he found
an interesting notebook in the Niji Forest.
Let’s have a tea party with the three of us to discuss that notebook.
Your "tea" means alcohol, doesn't it?
Of course.
Akari-san won’t come if I'm around.
Hey, you didn't address him as "sensei" either!
I'm an exception, because he doesn't like me.
That's not the point.
Please finish the job in front of you.
Have you been fooling around all this time?
Darn it.
I know, I know.
So did you find anything?
Nothing at all.
That's why we thought that there's no other way
except to ask this creature here directly.
Although, I don't think he'll answer our questions willingly.
Let's try asking anyway.
I'll give you a chance to atone for your sins.
Tell me everything about what you aimed to achieve with your actions,
and how you're related to Kafka.
Were you the one who distributed the drug?
Who do you think you're talking to?
What?
Foolish humans like you...
Eh?
Tell me about your relationship with Palnedo.
Hirato and the others are putting him to rest.
They've defeated that man.
He's dead...
The man who caused the deaths of Tsubaki and Yotaka is dead.
This should've been what I had strongly wished for.
And yet...
Gareki's heart is feeling the same as me.
A feeling of tightness...
I wonder if the reason I can't put my feelings to rest is because...
I didn't get to kill him with my own hands...
Meiga has been wiped out by them.
Meiga?
Who's that?
That boy...
Are you talking about Nai?
No, I'm talking about Gareki.
He was on that ship, right?
The ship that we sank back then.
I guess everything is predestined by fate, huh?
Well, I don't know.
Hirato-san.
You look like there's something you want to say, Yogi.
Back in the Niji Forest, Gareki was attacked by the bestial Varuga,
and yet he was unhurt.
From this, we deduced that they wanted to abduct him,
so we used him as bait.
The members from the First Ship were originally
in charge of the events that occurred here,
but you said you were coming here.
So you were partly here as a loan to the First Ship
members in order to attract the attention of that coward.
Also, if the ones who attacked Gareki appeared as well,
we would be killing two birds with one stone.
I'm sorry, Gareki-kun.
About what? That's part of your job, isn't it?
Damn it!
Well now,
may I ask you to come along with us?
Hold on!
What are you–
Tsubame...
Why are you going with them?
You're not alone, right?
Grandpa's still...
You'll still have people around–
Even you, Gareki...
Even you left me and went somewhere far away.
There's no one who remains by my side any more.
Why did you leave us?
We felt so lonely at home after you disappeared...
Well then, I'll be waiting here.
Just take your time to talk.
Yes, sir. Thank you for being so considerate.
I don't believe it! Someone from Circus?
He's so cool!
He's so cool, isn't he?
Grandpa.
It's Tsubame.
Grandpa, I've decided to leave the village.
I think it's possible I won't be able to come here again.
But, don't worry,
because the people of Circus will be taking good care of you.
Grandpa, please live to a ripe old age, okay?
I wonder who the old man in this ward is,
to have Circus come here for his sake?
Even the young man who paid his
hospital fees is such a mystery.
Which young man?
He also came by here yesterday, remember?
I think he's still in his teens.
He has black hair, and looks really dashing!
Oh, that young man–
Excuse me!
What's his name?!
Please tell me!
Now that you mention it, when your grandfather was still conscious,
I heard him calling the man "Gareki"...
Welcome home!
Huh? Where's Gareki?
I think Gareki is hanging out with bad
company and doing dangerous stuff.
What?
Forget about him.
He's a complete stranger to us now.
Gareki!
Are you finished with your business in Karasuna?
I could've settled everything for you if you had just told me...
that you were going to renew the lease for this land.
Are you trying to safeguard the grave of your family?
I have no family.
The reason why you left them was because
you didn't want to implicate them, isn't it?
What an adorable thing to do.
Shut up.
I was protected by so many people.
They gave me so much encouragement.
Are you finished with your visit?
I have a request.
With the remaining time left of my life...
I don't mind even if you have
to hurt me or cut me up,
I'm willing to...
I'm willing to offer my body as
a specimen in order to defeat Kafka!
I swear I'll not live a meaningless life.
Please make use of my body!
What a wonderful look.
Until the day my life comes to an end...
I'll gladly accept a gem like you.
I'll put you, who couldn't fly, onto my wings and we'll fly together!
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Akari-san, if you're so irritable, it'll have an adverse effect on your work.
If you know that, then get out of my sight now.
What a thing to say. To think that all along
I've had such a calming effect on you...
Score 7
「The Mermaid's Sigh」 and
the Three Knights
Stop disturbing me! Get out!