色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
You haven't eaten anything at all?
No...
Damn it!
I’ll get you something to eat.
Stay here and wait for me.
Nai, don't go anywhere, you understand?
Karoku...
Score 2
Fortune Cat
About last night's incident,
Things did not go smoothly, did they?
Second Ship Captain Hirato.
Your superior did not seem to provide you with proper discipline.
It's rude to make such derisive remarks when he's right here...
First Ship Captain, Tsukitachi.
Do not speak out of turn.
I will reflect on my mistakes and see that it does not happen again.
Very well.
You are dismissed.
They make such a fuss.
Old men are so stubborn with their stereotypes.
Why did you come with me?
Well, I thought I might enjoy watching you being reprimanded.
I will shoot you when I see you in the sky.
Moreover, the train jacking was supposed be our mission.
But, you took it over for us.
You owe me one...
Holy, that sounds expensive.
Come, come!
Here.
And so, after catching all the bad guys in the area,
they will put on a show to apologize for scaring the people.
A show?
Yes. A circus show.
Circus...
That's right.
Karoku.
Um?
Say, is there a person named Karoku in the Circus?
Well, I don't know.
Nana, we're going!
Sorry. Bye.
Thank you.
I've confirmed that boy's location.
Bring him in right away.
However, do not injure him.
Understood.
That brat!
I'm going to kill him...
H-Hey.
Here.
Come and see us, okay?
I, well...
Nyanperowna!
Hello. Please don't push.
Come here.
Damn it!
Huh?
Nai!
Dammit...
I-I-I am sorry!
Nyanperowna, are you all right?
Nyanta.
Nyansuke.
Gareki!
You... You wandered off by yourself, and got yourself chased!
That man...
He wasn't from the Security Forces...
Why's he chasing Nai?
In fact, who is he?
Let's go.
Who is the closest to area N11 now?
Me... it's Yogi.
Why are you in such a bad mood?
Wha– Please listen to me, Hirato-san!
First, I was knocked down by this boy who came zipping through.
Then, the people chasing after him stepped on my back so hard.
We've got information that the boy we met in the train is being chased.
After that, my head was even stepped on, and now it hurts...
We're going to protect him, aren't we?
Please let me go.
You are still in the middle of the performance.
Make sure the townsfolk enjoy the show.
Hello? Hey!
Hey, are you listening to me, Hirato-san?
Hey, Gareki.
What?
If I go to the Circus, maybe Karoku...
Not now.
I have to find out who that man was–
All right, I have incapacitated him.
Gareki!
Stop.
Gareki... Gareki... Gareki.
This brat is the one.
What? Then what should we do with this one?
It'll be troublesome if we leave him here.
This is bad.
I can't move...
Gareki!
Kill him.
These guys...
Gareki!
Hey! What are you guys doing?
Using such a dangerous thing on an innocent boy...
You're such bad guys.
Who the hell are you?!
Eat this!
Candy Bar!
Why are you chasing these boys?
In any case, I can't ignore such wicked deeds happening in front of me.
Ba. Ba. Ba!
Filled with the power of man's spirit!
I'm the Sparkling Prince who makes your hearts throb!
The Second Ship Fighter of the National Defense Organization, Circus, Yogi...
is here!
Circus...
Come, I will be your opponent.
Which one shall first...
What?
What the–?
Phew. What a relief.
I get so nervous when I fight.
Oh no, Nyanperowna got dirty.
Hey, are you two okay?
Good.
Listen, I was told to bring you two along with me,
so please follow me at once.
W-Well, I want to ask you something.
What? Can you wait for a moment?
This is Yogi.
Yes.
Really, are you already up there?
That was fast.
Circus was looking for us?
What does that mean?
Well, let's go.
Welcome to the Circus Ship!
I'm home!
Welcome back. Welcome back.
You two, answer, "I'm home."
I'm home.
Answer.
I’m home.
Voice recognition registration is completed.
I am happy to see you again, Gareki-kun, Nai-kun.
Let me introduce myself again.
I am Second Ship Captain of the National Defense Organization, Circus, Hirato.
I am one of the members who are in charge of eliminating crimes from this world.
Though actually, our specialty's to pursue special crimes.
Regular crimes are under the jurisdiction of the Security Forces–
Excuse me...
Is Karoku here?
I only found this, and there was this crimson liquid... I mean, blood...
Gareki told me we should ask Circus since this belongs to Circus.
You've got it wrong.
There is no one named Karoku among the members of Circus.
That bracelet is certainly a Circus I.D.
But it's an older model which should have been destroyed.
Depending on your cooperation, we may be able
to find some clues about that person, Karoku.
Yes, I will cooperate!
By the way, Gareki-kun,
you know a woman named Mine, don't you?
No.
I really find it adorable when I see young people acting tough.
There's no need to be scared.
Who are you calling scared–
We found traces of blast marks at Mine's house.
Your skill disposing of the bombs on the train was superb, too.
Is it your way of showing consideration by choosing wealthy targets...
who had gotten their riches through ill-gotten gains?
I wonder why you need such a great amount of money.
Oh sorry, I have no intention of persecuting you.
When you were in contact with Mine, did her blood splash on you?
What was that monster?
"Varuga."
We are after the criminal organization which has created those...
awful monsters in the name of "Evolution."
If their blood gets into your body, you will become like Mine.
We will examine both of you.
I regret to say you have no right to refuse.
Woo, this is too serious.
Why are you talking so authoritatively, Hirato-san?
Oh, I didn't know you were here, Yogi.
What?
Oh, Gareki-kun,
you did not kill Mine.
Are you relieved?
You don't like killing, do you?
Circus got in your way?
It's close to the town of Gavan.
Sure, you can ask for "their" help.
The blue flower blooms from blue seeds.
But I am looking for red seeds.
The Second Ship Captain, Hirato.
That young punk.
We will be heading to the town of Earthen Grounds, Gavan.
I will leave Gareki and Nai's care to the two of you.
Sure.
Why us?
Is it because you think we are not as good as the others?
It's because I trust you.
They've gotten away from Varuga, so there's a
possibility that they will become the enemy's target.
Guarding someone is also an important assignment.
Do you understand, Tsukumo?
I'm sorry.
Gareki, something was flying.
What?
Speaking of which, the ship has landed.
Gareki?
What? Gareki-kun, what are you doing?
I'm going into town.
What, what, what, no, no, no, no, no.
It's so late.
Let me go shopping.
What? What are you buying?
Things like clothes.
Clothes? We have clothes. We have all sorts of clothes!
Well, there is nothing to do.
It's boring.
Well then, let's play hide and seek!
What? How old are you?
Well, I am 21 years old.
But there are times when even adults want to play hide and seek!
I will be "it".
What?
But ordinary people usually cannot keep up with me,
so you don't have to play if you don't think you are up to the challenge.
The time limit is one hour.
One, two, three, four, five...
That place is off-limits.
Huh?
Off-limits. Off-limits. Off-limits. Off-limits...
Off-limits.
Yogi.
Off-limits. Off-limits.
Hey, stop, stop.
Hide and seek,
somewhere where I can't be found.
Whoa,
I found red seeds.
Since you came to me, why are you running away?
Yogi, all victims seemed to have been deliberately killed.
It's highly possible that this is a diversion.
Strengthen the security around Gareki and Nai.
It's too late!
Tsukumo-chan!
Oh no!
Nai-chan, run away!
Run, you dork!
Run away as fast as you can!
What are you doing?
You're the main target, aren't you?!
Gareki...
Run!
No way...
Release...
Release everyone!
Our mission is to bring back the red seed.
All right!
She couldn't find you after one hour, right?
Huh?
Hide and seek is over.
That Varuga was trying to take Nai-kun.
Capture without killing, huh...
That was scary, wasn't it?
Let's take a warm bath.
Bath...
Nai, Nai...
I wonder if you can hear me well?
Nai.
Karoku, what are you doing?
I'm kissing.
I heard you were involved in an incident, Erisyuka.
Karoku!
Karoku, I've wanted to see you!
K-Karoku....
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Ah...
What happened ~ma?
Well, am I doing okay with Nyanperowna?
It’s average ~ma.
What?
The sales of Nyanperowna merchandises haven't been changing ~ma.
What? I am going to work harder to become popular!
Score 3
Phantom Picnic
Try your best ~ma.