色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Gareki-kun!
Akari-sensei, please take care of Nai-chan!
Gare... ki.
I must believe... that he's all right!
Score 4
Evening Swallow
Ga...
Gareki-kun.
Sapphire Crown.
I command stones to bury evil with their dazzling brilliance.
I am known as the Queen of the Crown,
Second Ship Fighter, National Defense Organization, Circus, Iva.
Those who do not accept my love shall be smashed to pieces!
Iva-neesan!
You fool!
Dork!
Be thankful to me!
Can you get up, boy?
Don't overdo it.
Does it hurt anywhere?
Do you feel strange anywhere?
Or feel nauseous?
Sorry.
You're so scared that you can't even talk, right?
I should have tried harder to protect you!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
You've got it wrong!
I'm only silent because I'm trying to figure out what's going on!
Let go of me!
Hey, just leave him alone.
Nee-san, why are you here?
I was chasing a Varuga from Gavan.
But he was quick to run away.
Reluctantly, I was going to head back,
when that Bestial Varuga appeared out of nowhere.
So I decided to take it out on him.
Bestial Varuga?
It's the beast form of a Varuga.
So that was also...
Even looking at a man's face doesn't comfort me.
It has to be a cute creature.
Didn't Tsukumo come with you?
In human terms, I would say that it's suffering from bruises..
Bruises?
It's okay. It will get better soon.
I wonder if Gareki and Yogi are okay.
It's because I acted on my own, isn't it?
You're absolutely right.
However, you aren't the main cause of this.
The ones who attacked us are.
Why did they attack Gareki, instead of Nai?
The examination results showed no signs of Varuga blood cells in either of them.
There you are.
Akari-sensei!
Is Gareki injured?
He was reeling.
It was so slow walking along with him.
Why is Iva....
I'll kiss you if you struggle again.
Gareki-kun, it would have been better to be carried on my back.
Please, just kill me.
I don't see any major problems.
But just as a precaution, you should go back to the ship with Iva.
Gareki, I'm sorry.
Huh? For what?
Because I...
Anyway, are you all right?
Mm-hm.
Well, there were some interruptions,
but let's get back to our original mission.
I hope that there's still something related to Nai and Karoku left.
Ka-Karoku?
So, this is where Nai-chan and Karoku-san stayed.
I'm sorry, but we'll be messing up the place.
Yogi.
Roger.
Come, look here.
Do you understand?
I understand.
That's good.
Karoku is... warm.
It's warm.
Karoku-sama,
please get ready.
If I touch this light, I wonder if I would cry because of its warmth.
I'll be right there.
Why did you fail?!
Even if you ask that, Erisyuka-sama, it's not easy when Circus is around.
Karoku showed some interest in that boy, Gareki.
I wanted to surprise him by bringing that boy here.
He always has the same expression no matter what I give him.
I want him to like me even more.
He already likes you very much.
Erisyuka-sama is 14 years old and Karoku-sama is 18 years old.
Based on your ages, you two are a great match.
I want something more! I want him to forcefully catch me even if I resist!
I want him to become infatuated with me,
and desperately want me.
Uro, what should I do?
Let's see... that's a tough one.
There's nothing that interests me.
Even Nai-chan said they weren't doing anything out of the ordinary.
Right, Nai-chan?
A bug is coming out.
A bug?
Sensei?
Yogi, move this rock.
O-Okay.
What? Something is...
Oh, Tsukumo!
Hooray, it's lunch!
Wow, it's gorgeous.
Did you make this Tsukumo-chan?
It looks so yummy.
Here, Nai-chan, sandwiches.
Eat quickly.
Our mission is done.
We're wasting time.
Hey, enjoy the food more, Sensei.
Tsukumo brought them just for us.
Right, Tsukumo?
Iva...
Gareki. Is your wound okay?
I'm not hurt.
Just eat your food.
Did you find anything?
Yes. A notebook.
I took a look inside, but I couldn't understand any of it.
It was all numbers and signs.
I'm sorry to say... it's impossible for me to decipher.
But, Akari-sensei went through it pretty thoroughly.
I see.
I've a favor to ask of you.
Welcome back. Welcome back.
I'm back.
No way, I'm definitely going!
Hirato-san.
No you aren't.
Good afternoon.
I'm going!
We're leaving Niji Forest now.
I'm telling you... you can't come with me–
It seems that Karasuna, the place where Gareki-kun used to live, is somewhere nearby,
so he's saying there's a place he wants to stop by.
Let go.
Really?
Are you kidding? Did he say yes?
Hirato is too nice.
He gives me the creeps!
Didn't I report that they were attacked by a Bestial Varuga?
That's why Yogi is with them.
Iva and Tsukumo, guard the Research Tower group.
Akari-san is there, isn't he?
Let me talk to him.
Hirato-san wants to say thank you for various things.
There's no need to.
Just hang up.
He's supposed to be a grown-up, right?
What?
"You're such a sweet person, expressing your likes and dislikes in such a straightforward manner."
I'm supposed to tell him that?
No way!
If you want to fight, please do it in person.
You two are like cats and dogs.
And so that's how it went.
Oh well, I owe you one again.
Good for you, Nai-chan.
The captain says you can go with him.
He'll just be in my way!
Nai-chan is afraid of being separated from Gareki-kun.
What?
I guess I've got no choice.
Hooray!
It's been a long time since I wandered around in a town.
Don’t put on a foolish face or your pocket will be picked.
That’s like Gareki.
Damn it!
Wow, I want that leather bracelet.
Can I give it a try?
What?
Huh?
Why?
Why can't I hit it?
You're pathetic.
Give it to me.
Whooooa, you're so cool!
What? Are you finished with your business?
Gareki?
Gareki-kun, wait up!
Eh?
Tsubame?
I'm glad.
I'm so happy to see you.
Did something happen?
I... I... I...
killed a man.
What should I do?
I didn't know you moved.
No wonder you weren't home no matter how many times I visited.
I think it's been around two years since you last came over, right?
Um...
Why...?
Um, what's your relationship with Gareki-kun, Tsubame-chan?
You're not his little sister... are you?
Relative?
Um...
Or maybe his girlfriend?
Y-You're wrong! My dream is to marry a chubby man with gentle eyes!
That's the total opposite of him, right?
Where is Yotaka?
Um, I haven’t told Yotaka.
But, he may already know that something has happened.
Oh yeah, both of you are twins so you could always sense the other's feelings.
Why did you kill?
Nai-chan, you're too straightforward!
I've always felt sick from time to time.
That feeling has gotten worse recently.
I spaced out, and then when I came to, I found blood on my clothes.
I couldn't remember anything.
But it was different yesterday.
You bastards, what are you doing to Tsubame!
Stop, you've got it all wrong.
It's Gareki!
Gareki.
Oh...You're still alive...
I wonder if it's okay.
It's a stranger's house after all.
Tsubame said the owner of this house fled away during the night.
Well, that's why I'm asking if we're really doing the right thing.
Speaking of which, there aren't many residents in this village.
Has it always been like this?
Of course not.
Gareki-kun, what is your relation to those two?
Well, is it okay to ask?
Let's see... I think I was about eight years old, when my parents sold me.
I was crowded into the hold of a ship with other kids who were also sold.
And then, it started.
Senseless bullying of the weak.
I wasn't really weak, but I became a target because I was the smallest of everyone.
I was tied up and my two meals per day were taken away.
That's when I noticed there was something strange about those meals.
Those kids gradually broke down after a few days...
When I thought I was too tired to walk any more, I was rescued by Tsubaki.
Tsubaki saved my life.
And her little brother and sister are Yotaka and Tsubame.
Tsubaki was betrayed and killed by a man she loved.
I don't know the face of the man who killed her.
But if I ever meet him, I will kill him.
Huh?
Can I embrace you?
What?
The love felt from an embrace, the broken heart of the child will...
You're the child yourself!
I don't like killing.
Gareki, killing is not good.
Gareki-kun!
You two... are so annoying!
I have a brother and a sister about the same age as you.
That's probably why...
I just couldn't leave you alone.
There's someone I love.
The drug is from him.
It should be safe.
Are you stupid?
Don't trust him.
He got me out of the shop.
He's also paying for Grandpa’s hospital expenses.
It's just a nutritional supplement.
He said he just wanted data on the twins.
Aren't you actually suspicious?
That they're being used for some weird experiment.
Because by myself I cannot feed them, protect them, or even buy things they need.
Even for you Gareki, I have nothing...
I don't need anything.
If it's about money, I'll come up with it somehow.
So don't you ever go to his place again.
Didn't I tell you not to go?!
Shh.
Outside... Tsubame-chan...
Have you been awake all this time?
Huh? Um well...
You've suspected it ever since you heard Tsubame's story.
I'm... sorry.
It's okay. I'd thought of it, too.
If Tsubame is...
Why? When?
Wait, I bet it was those drugs from back then.
Then, the man who made use of and then killed Tsubaki...
Say, can they possibly return to their original selves?
I understand...
A picture's drawn there.
That's not a picture.
That's an injury.
I've seen that pattern somewhere before.
It's similar to the marks on Tsubaki's corpse.
In that case, it's the same person.
I don't know the face of the man who killed her.
But if I ever meet him, I will kill him.
I will  definitely kill him.
Yotaka!
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Akari-chan, welcome back.
Aren't there any souvenirs?
It was work. I didn't go there for a vacation.
Eh? Then what's that in your chest pocket?
This is a Hana-Usagi.
That is not fair, Akari-chan!
What's not fair?
Score 5
Clown Prescription