Crap.
What's with this guy?
Yogi.
Kagiri-san!
Oh, no...
色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Yukkin!
Nai-kun, what's the matter?
Yogi. Yogi.
Nai-kun!
Yogi. Yogi. Yogi. Yogi. Yogi. Yogi. Yogi.
Don't tell me they were both killed by those Varuga.
Nai-kun, hide here, and please promise me not to move an inch.
I'll be back soon.
Score 9
Blue Rose
Tsukumo-chan!
If I tell Uro-san we were defeated by Circus, he's definitely gonna kill us.
Say, aren't you the girl who escaped earlier?
Varuga.
What happened to my comrades?
So that's how you look underneath that hood.
Wow...
Amazingly cute!
Answer me!
How should I know?
That blond guy completely lost it all of a sudden.
The black-haired brat must be dead by now!
It can't be true.
But from the way Nai-kun reacted, something must've happened.
You let down your guard.
This is it!
Nai-kun... Yogi...
Yahoo!
Tsukumo-chan.
Tsukumo-chan!
Karoku-sama...
Is something wrong?
Are you all right?
Uro, I have a headache, so I want to rest a little bit.
We still have some time until the party.
Please take your time and rest.
Tsukumo-chan, huh?
I hear you. Scream more, Nai.
I wonder why I protected you.
He doesn't recognize me.
What's happening to him?
Yogi.
What? You want to play?
Want to play, my ass!
Ow...
That's so mean, Ga...Ga...
Ga... What... Gare.
Oh no, Gareki-kun!
I'm so glad you're okay.
Have I been unconscious?
I'm so sorry.
Thank goodness you're still warm...
Nai?
Gareki.
Tsukumo-chan...
Tsukumo-chan was…
I'm sorry for waking you from your sleep.
Time has no meaning to the people of Research Tower.
Ah... Right.
Let Nai and Gareki wait there after their medical examination.
Um, is there anything I can do?
You belong to the Life Division, so this is not in your expertise.
But if it has to do with Varuga, I want to…
Azana, I understand that you feel you can't stand by and do nothing.
Since your family was killed by Varuga, you feel as if it's happening to you.
After you finish your report, get some rest.
Where am I?
I can't find Uro-san.
Help me look for him too, Kagiri-san!
Should I just shout for him, with all my momentum?
We came here without telling him, stupid Kiharu.
We'll get scolded if we attract any attention.
You're giving me hard time.
You're so mean, Uro.
Being in that crowd made Karoku-sama feel sick. He told me that he wanted to be alone.
I don't like it. It's so boring!
Where are you going, Erisyuka-sama?
The bathroom.
Don't follow me!
I'll look for him in secret.
Maybe Karoku is at the rooftop.
Gathering of people with masks...
What's going on?
There's no connection here.
The radio signal is being blocked.
Should I just go ahead and check things out?
No.
I must get out of here right away.
Oh no, why are you injured like that?
Erisyuka...
I think I've met you somewhere before...
Erisyuka-sama!
There was someone…
Find her!
Yes sir!
Uro!
What happened?
The girl from Circus that I met at the train was here... and she was bleeding!
What? That girl escaped?!
Who are these people?
Please forget that you ever saw them.
They have absolutely no part in your brilliant life.
Escort her to the room.
Yes, sir.
Well, uh...
Uro-san?
Why are you here?
What have you done?
Oh... Well...
I-It's a rather long story.
Why are you guys so stupid?
Do you have a death wish?
Find that Circus girl.
Half dead is fine!
Bring her to me.
There's nothing wrong with either of you.
But as a precaution, you'll be staying here tonight.
Did you find Tsukumo-chan?
I told you the Second Ship is going all out to find her, didn't I?
Is Yogi…
What are the results of the examination?
Both of them have no problems in terms of the numerical data.
Ikami, thanks for a job well done.
Nai, Gareki, come with me.
Here's some tea.
Excuse me...
Take some liquids.
How's Yogi?
I'm about to talk about that.
I have a few questions for you.
Questions?
Have you finished his examination?
We've given him appropriate medical procedure.
So he's sleeping now.
Tell me in detail about what happened before and after Yogi's transformation.
Anything will do.
When I saw Yogi again, he didn't have that white thing on his face.
Do you mean the patch?
I also noticed it wasn't there when we returned.
But if he transforms just for losing his patch,
won't the same thing happen again once he gets it replaced?
Eh?
You weren't there when it happened, but he changed big time,
even the color of his hair.
It was almost like…
Gareki.
When was the patch removed?
Huh? So you think?
Yes, it's related to that.
But as you said,
I don't make faulty things that cease
to work the instant they come off.
Is he mentally sick?
It's nothing like that.
It occasionally afflicts people
who take on the special duties of Circus.
It's an allergy.
He's hiding a lot of details behind his words.
Give me a proper explanation.
I was caught up in that, you know.
I think I have a right to know.
Good grief. I'm the one asking questions.
Yogi's sudden transformation in this incident is something irregular.
I received a report stating that there was a interaction with Varuga.
Other than that, was there anything else different in Yogi?
He was scared and cried in the room full of dolls.
Dolls? Was that at the mansion which you investigated?
No, to be precise, it was
a hidden room beneath the mansion.
Speaking of which, what were the contents of the box Yogi brought back?
What? Box?
Wasn't it in his overcoat?
The rusty box that was making clattering noises.
No, he didn't have it.
But tell me the details.
Uro-san, well, this is...
Ki-Kiharu picked it up during the battle.
I got caught up in my momentum and thought it was Kagiri-san's toy.
If Circus had gotten hold of this, it would have been used as evidence against us.
It could've given a breakthrough to the government.
Circus, toys of the cowardly government.
They've captured people who were drawn to us,
but those people know nothing, just like lizard tails.
We can easily replace them.
It's about Erisyuka-sama.
Tell me about it later.
But for the tails, we, the body, are something they long for forever.
That's why they will never stop cooperating with us.
Because things we're selling them are the love and hope they've been seeking.
Bestial Varuga...
Even if I fight recklessly and kill these creatures in front of me,
there's a greater chance that new enemies will appear.
I'm all alone right now.
I should only think about getting back alive.
But...
If I fail to escape...
I'll kill myself with my own hands before being captured.
I have to make sure I don't leave anything behind. I won't let them use my body for themselves.
I should've talked with everyone more.
I should've stayed together with them more.
That's because I trust you.
I'm counting on you, Tsukumo.
Hirato...
How could I have such negative thoughts?
He believed in me. He relied on me.
I'm not going to end my life.
I am a member of Circus!
I'll only die for my friends!
At this point, it's just a presumption,
but that box probably contained parts of the Varuga body or something with similar components.
It has been left around for a long time,
so the components spilled out and possibly filled the air.
If that idiot had forgotten to replace the patch,
the effects of containing his allergic reaction would probably be reduced to near zero.
Even then, the chances of him going berserk is less than 50 percent.
Then why?
It's a different story if he had inhaled the air containing Varuga components.
Having Varuga components inside of his body... would greatly increase the allergic substances within him.
He's hiding something again.
When the patch came off,
the balance between the allergic substances and his own cells broke down,
causing him to go berserk.
His condition sounds pretty unstable.
Say, I've been wanting to ask this,
but what's the mechanism behind Circus members flying and drawing weapons out of nowhere?
You should ask that to Hirato–well no, Tsukitachi.
Both Yogi and Tsukumo are currently incapactitated,
so apparently for the time being, you two will be sent to the First Ship.
Lack of sleep will weaken your body.
Go to sleep now.
Nai.
Huh?
You totally didn't understand the conversation earlier, did you?
I sort of understood it.
Liar.
I really do, Gareki.
Compared to back then, somehow I understand things more now.
I can tell when you're thinking of Yotaka-san and others.
When you're sleeping in the room, I can sense things falling from above you.
Feelings of sadness, pain, and suffering...
I've never tried asking you because you're
always your usual self when you're awake.
You know, it's always quiet at night, so I'm able to hear even the smallest of voices.
So If I sleep by the window, I may hear Tsukumo-chan's voice.
I wonder if everyone gets involved in
dangerous things because I'm with them.
Is that so, Karoku?
This isn't good, Kagiri-san!
If we don't find that girl, we will seriously be killed.
We definitely must find her.
Please don't let out your voice.
If you do, I will break your neck.
Please, put your hands up to your head.
What... a hidden needle.
I'm sorry, Tsukumo-chan.
Thank you for being kind to Nai.
Nai, it's okay to burst into tears of joy, okay?
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
On your mark
Erisyuka-sama wants to see you, Karoku-sama.
Ready
Bam!
Me too.
Very well. I will tell her so.
Nai, where are you now?
Karoku-sama?
Score 10
Tears of the Beast Handler
Nai.