Karoku.
Nai. Come here.
If I were...
Karoku.
Where have you gone?
Are you nervous?
You are pushing my stomach.
Makes me nauseous.
You're heavy.
What do you mean I make you nauseous.
These are Karoku's.
The Circus I.D.
Did they... find us?
What was that? Intruders?
Check it!
KARNEVAL
Darn it. There's only junk.
Score 1
Rainbow Colored Flower Fuse
Excuse me...
What?
Ah, are you going to escape?
I want to escape, too.
But...
You have something interesting.
I might be able to take you out of here.
Really?
But, only on one condition.
That bracelet, give it to me.
Sure, but this is Karoku's.
If Karoku says you can have it, it's okay with me.
It's a deal.
Damn it. She's back.
Are you with Circus?
You can't be...
You're just a little thief, aren't you?
So what?
It's fine. Run away.
What?
Let's play tag.
But I will catch you soon!
What are you?
Hey, come on!
Welcome back, Tsukumo-chan.
I was having a cup of tea while I was waiting for you.
Hey, we're in public.
Yes, yes, don't worry.
I am concealing my presence.
No one noticed me, right?
Jeez...
Anyway, report what Mine, the proprietor of the Karasuna, has to say.
As we expected.
We will leave right away.
Damn it.
Come out!
Move one step, the wings are torn...
Move two steps, the innards are gone...
Mine-sama!
I tracked down the intruders here!
Move three steps, you become a feast for death.
Mine-sama?
Well, that didn't work out like I expected.
If I don't eat enough, I won't be able to move fast enough.
What is... she?
Yes, that's right.
Got it.
Check–
Didn't I say a tag, not hide-and-seek?
You have to run farther.
U-Um...
what happened to her?
I only ever have three choices.
Enemy, nobody, or prey.
Well..
This one is...
I am Gareki, and you?
Nai.
Palnedo, CEO of Gardo Corporation, how do you like to ride in the cattle-class?
It must be very different from first-class.
What are you going to do with me?
It hurts.
That damn brat...
What?
Whoa, I didn't know you were here.
What a surprise.
It's kind of a mess...
You could have lived longer if you had stuck with collecting money.
Hey, don't fall behind!
Smoke?
Oh well, another dead end...
They got away again.
This woman, Mine, was the one we had the evidence on.
So close...
What's wrong?
Yes, I regret to say they made the first move here.
Train jacking?
The Security Force is already on the move?
All right, I understand.
Security Force?
They're already making a move?
Dammit!
What about over there?
This is not good.
Leaving town seems to be the only option.
But this town's exit gates must be closed by now.
Listen,
when I give the signal, you jump off.
Y-Yes.
Let's go!
Karoku...
This can't be real.
Why was the proprietor of the Karasuna such a monster...
Um...
Thank you for helping me.
Why were you in captivity?
Well, I was looking for Karoku...
What does this Karoku have to do with you?
Karoku was always with me.
But...
Ah?
Karoku didn't come home for a long time so I got lonely.
So I went to look for him.
I saw many red puddles, large and small, leading toward the ocean.
Then, I found this there.
You talk oddly...
Rather, that was blood, wasn't it?
He got involved in some mess and got abducted, didn't he?
If not, he was dragged to the ocean and thrown in.
Come to think of it, she said this bracelet was a Circus I.D.
From his story, I can't think of Karoku as a member of Circus.
I can't work in Karasuna for a little while.
Even if I don't get that bracelet, I can probably get some kind of reward.
I won't lose anything.
I wonder how long it's been since I last saw Karoku.
I want to eat with him.
My body hurts in many places.
Karoku.
Hey you, what are you doing?
I heard a strange sound.
Sound?
I don't hear anything strange.
Now that you mention it, there are no passengers...
Gareki, where are you going?
There is something strange going on.
I'm going to check it out.
You will be in the way so stay here...
Gareki.
I never thought the hijackers would have a kid as their lookout.
In the back, there was a noise.
Who's there?
Who are you guys?
What are you doing here?
If you two are not in their group, you should have told me.
Answer me!
Come again?
Dammit.
Tsukumo, let's go.
Yes, sir.
Darn it.
Gareki.
Well, we seem to be caught up in something annoying.
Even so, who was that guy in black?
That sound from before.
What?
Up front.
Hey!
Listen, if you move an inch,
we will shoot them.
Why can't we beat them?
By the looks of it, they are ordinary citizens.
It will cause trouble if we step out of our jurisdiction.
You ruined our lives!
In order for the company to survive, laying off workers was unavoidable.
You say that is evil,
but you are doing even worse by getting my innocent granddaughter involved.
Shut up! Shut up!
Here!
Who are you guys?
Where did you come from?
Crap!
Come out you brats!
Isn't that enough?
You'd better stop it.
It is only a sad foolish act if you are causing this destruction in order to release your frustrations.
Shut up!
The bombs we set in each carriage will start to explode one by one...
If you stop the train, all of them will explode at once...
Are you serious?
We were planning on taking Palnedo with us from the beginning.
I am sorry to say, you will all be coming with us.
Tsukumo, take these two somewhere safe.
I will take care of the bombs.
Yes.
Well, who are you two?
I am the Second Ship Captain, Hirato, of the National Defense Organization, Circus.
I am the Second Ship fighter, Tsukumo.
There is a girl like you in Circus?
Yes.
What?
He reacted before the explosion.
Sound.
Sound?
There is electrical interference.
Tsukumo,
the worst case scenario is to evacuate everyone and derail the train.
There will be residential areas from here on.
Electrical interference?
It can't be.
But, it's too late to think after your dead.
We have to make sure not to slow down.
Hey, four-eyed shithead!
Four-eyed shithead?
Get over here.
There's still a chance.
Come here!
Nai, where is that sound coming from?
Here.
Stand back.
There it is!
But this isn't a bomb.
Just an electric jammer.
There are a bunch of fakes.
The base is made by ST, electrically ignited, the route to ignite the explosion is this.
And this is the electric detection device.
This one is not connected with radio wave induction.
This thing hasn't synchronized with the radio transmitter yet.
The point is, we have to separate the back of the train before the radio waves reach it.
That answer is worth trusting.
Stand back, both of you.
Vakuum!
Gareki, where are you going?
I am taking off before the Security Force finds me.
Um... Gareki.
What?
Thank you.
Come again?
You saved me again.
Is it all right?
The bracelet that boy had...
You recognized it, didn't you?
Of course.
But now...
Excuse me.
Can you spare me a few minutes?
I do not wish to refuse to cooperate with the investigation,
but I have been feeling a pain in my chest for some time now.
Well...
I am quite old as you can see.
And my doctor is here to see me. I am sorry but I will have to excuse myself.
Then, we'll talk some other time.
I took care of the Karasuna incident.
Well, you look exhausted.
I let myself be captured on purpose to see how effective Circus is.
They are as I expected.
Please do not play around too much.
If there is a need, we will always take action.
Speaking of which, I saw someone interesting.
He seems to have some unique ears.
He looks little bit like "him."
Can you capture him?
Hirato of Circus seems to be interested in him too.
It's done!
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Tsukumo
These, snacks–they seem strange?
I bought them at a café in Karasuna.
Muffins, scones, short breads.
There are so many.
These are souvenirs for Yogi.
Treating him like a child–?
Score 2
Fortune Cat