Jiki-kun...
Rainbow. I want to go there.
It might be Karoku!
I want to go!
You may be right.
It's a little creepy, almost as if we're being sent an invitation.
Shall we go?
Yes.
They're so easy to read.
It's obvious that they don't want us to go near that place.
Score 13
Karneval
Gareki-kun!
Crate of Thorns!
It's too dangerous for you, Gareki-kun.
I'll take you back to the ship right away.
You're going to where that rainbow is, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm sure over there–
I know. I slow you down.
I haven't been keeping up with your speed at all.
I'm such a freaking burden.
Sorry, but can you please take me with you?
Uh, um, ah, Gareki-kun.
Gareki-kun...
To tell you the truth, I also wanted you to come with me.
Let's go save Nai-chan together.
Azana, you're confused!
You should be aware that you're talking nonsense!
We're weak.
Even Murano who cares so much about the creatures in Vinto
sought the powers of Varuga.
Were you the one who used my name in order to provide drugs for him?
Everyone trusts your name, Akari-sensei.
I don't want to do anything violent but I want you to come with me.
Hirato...
Ak-Akari-sensei, I've very much
looked up to you.
Your strong mind... I've always
admired it... from the shadows...
But why are you so talented?
Why do you even exist?!
I feel so miserable and hate myself.
And I hate you as well!
National Defense Organization, Research Tower, Life Division member, Azana.
Treason's a very serious crime.
According to regulations,
I can execute you promptly.
Hirato, don't do it!
Wait, Azana!
We've been letting him run free in order to get concrete evidence.
Ikami will chase him wherever Azana goes.
Azana...
Woohoo!
Hey there.
The bug in the last dungeon!
What?
Woohoo!
Honestly!
Don't get in my way, Tsuki-chan.
Kiichi, good job.
Holding back?
Banshees continuously adjust the pressure of
their binds when the target is to be captured alive.
In the current situation,
they're balancing its power in order to prohibit my movements
without killing me.
But right at that moment, I managed to make a hole underneath my stomach.
A hole of summoning
for my servants to emerge from.
Raise the pressure!
Fools!
The balance has already been broken!
Trying to capture me by only using remotely controlled banshees...
The Second Ship Captain is taking me pretty lightly, isn't he?
As we speak, worms of Circus are being attracted to the rainbow's light.
I will exterminate all of you in one go.
Your madness ends here.
I should be the one saying that!
Damn it.
Get out of my way!
Huh?
Hey, that's confusing.
You cracked your whip so hard!
It was a close call!
Yogi! Gareki!
Yo.
Nai-chan.
Aren't you scared? Are you okay?
Don't lower your guard.
The bottom of the rainbow is over there.
Karoku...
Would you like to sleep with a mother's embrace?
I'll give you eternal slumber before the door is closed.
There's a time limit?
Jiki-kun!
I'll take care of things here.
Got it.
That is…
Yogi!
Crate of Thorns!
Iva!
Tsukumo-chan!
Run, Nai!
Let us make it. Let us make it!
Find your way here by following the calm sound of flowing air.
This is the inside of a large shell.
Even the minuscule sounds of flapping wings will multiply and echo beautifully.
Even if it's a space where there's nothing but emptiness, if you go there, a miracle will happen.
Give me the key to the door!
If you don't, I'll take your head off at this very moment!
Impatient members of Circus,
this situation right now...
It is a box of secrets for us as well.
It can only be opened from the inside.
What are you–?
Nai.
Karoku.
Karoku!
Nai.
Karoku, you're alive.
Your wounds... are you okay?
That's Karoku?
Rather, where the heck is this?
Hey, Nai. Someone is lying on the ground.
Why are you ignoring–?
I can't move my body.
Say, can I give this to Gareki?
Work, my voice!
I promised him when he saved my life.
My voice!
Nai!
Something's wrong, you fool!
Karoku?
Karoku!
Huh? That's Karoku?
Blood. There's lots of blood.
I wanted him to see you for one last time.
I spoke for his wish and called you, Nai.
To come right away.
He was happy to be able to see you again, Nai.
In fact, his time should've ended in a place of emptiness.
I'm happy to see you for the first time,
since we've only talked so far.
But the part of Karoku who had lived with you at Niji forest is also now inside me.
I am now Karoku, Nai.
You wouldn't wear old clothes you can't use anymore, would you?
It's the same thing.
Did I surprise you?
Come with me, Nai.
You're such a good boy for coming all the way here.
It's natural for you to be on this side of the world.
Damn it.
Rise, my arm!
You should properly say good-bye to Gareki-kun.
You can't stay with him forever.
I don't want to. You're different.
Nai, you're being difficult.
If I break Gareki-kun, there would be nothing to hold you back anymore, right?
Stop it!
Don't mess with me!
This is bad. His pulse is…
I guess I have no choice.
If you need to play more, I'll wait.
I have a big heart, after all.
Nai.
Go and play as much as you want.
Launching an attack without our authorization.
Are you aware of how much confusion was created in order to clean up the mess
due to what you have done, Circus?
This incident was ordered by me.
I will take full responsibility.
All the same, I should share part of the blame for supporting the attack.
I'm aware of what we have done, but I would also like you to look at our results.
Results? Who are you kidding?
You couldn't even catch sight of Palnedo.
And that Palnedo is claiming that everything this time was all masterminded by Uro without his knowledge
and that he is innocent.
On top of that, you also failed to capture Uro.
Furthermore, Azana,
who is accused of treason, is also missing!
By the way, how is Karoku, the person reported as your rescue target?
Karoku was brought in with the condition of cardiac arrest.
He was revived by the treatment received by Doctor Akari.
But has yet to regain consciousness.
Karoku...
Nai-kun. Let's go back to the ship for now.
Okay.
Answer me!
I'm asking if there's any special way to enter, like taking a test,
even if I don't have a family register?
You mean the government's School?
What do you want to study there?
I really hate the Varugas and Kafka and all those guys...
They killed both Tsubaki and Yotaka.
They made Tsubame and Nai cry a lot.
I feel so upset about that.
At first, I thought if I stayed here, I could have my revenge on Kafka some day.
But I felt so uncool just staying around without being of any help at all.
That's why I want to learn new techniques and get some credentials.
And one day be able to beat Varuga.
Then I'll be able to... stay here with my head up.
Hey–
I'm saying I want to make this my job!
Why are you so excited all of a sudden?
I've been patiently listening to you.
I've researched many books
but not a single one mentioned on how a person without a family register could get into school.
I got it.
In that case, I'll get you tossed in there.
Into the School.
However, my responsibility for dragging you around stops there.
Any results beyond that point
will be entirely up to you.
It's not that easy.
I look forward to finding out if you will come back to our world.
Such results are obvious!
So he's not here...
Before we went to the Smoky Mansion,
he talked with Hirato-san.
Yukkin
No way. I want everyone to be here.
Everyone together...
Nai-kun...
Yogi...
I guess we should be happy,
as it's what Gareki-kun himself has chosen...
When Gareki-kun asked me what it meant to be a child of the Second Ship,
I became awfully worried.
I mean, to the world we don't really exist, right?
When I joined Circus,
in order not to endanger my family,
and at the same time not let me be shackled down by that,
both my family register and data were modified.
This is the only place I can call home.
I meet lots of people outside,
but even if I became friendly with them,
in the end everyone would say good-bye and move on.
That's why...
When Nai-chan and Gareki-kun came here,
I was very happy.
It felt like a breath of fresh air from outside,
and I was so excited.
But now for Gareki-kun, he will go through many things,
and meet many people whom he would hold dear out there.
So...
Gareki!
Gareki-kun!
You guys...
Gareki-kun... um...
Gareki...
You mustn't cry.
Gareki-kun would feel awkward.
Gareki-kun...
Think of him as me, and talk to him whenever you're having a hard time...
You mean you talk to this thing?!
Gareki-kun, um...
What?
I-I'm still bad at this,
but I made this with Nai-kun.
A Niji plushy...
Think of this as Nai-kun...
It's kind of ugly
and awfully deformed...
Thank you.
Gareki...
Here.
Karoku... is still asleep, right?
Yes...
Then make sure you ask him before we meet again.
That if it's okay to give me that.
Okay. I'll keep on calling out to Karoku.
Gareki-kun!
Gareki!
What shall I do if we never meet again?!
Be my reason
Everything...
subete ga ima
Be my power, future
Yogi! Nai-kun!
But...
ugokidasu
By your side...
After all...
Be my reason
Hey.
Starts moving now
kimi no soba de
Wait a minute!
Be my power, future
So you guys think I wouldn't be able to get my credentials and come back here?
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
kanjou no namae nante
Huh?
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
There'll be no end to it
Don't you want me to come back?
Huh?
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
Credentials for... what?
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
honnou de kikiwakeru
Didn't you hear anything from that shitty four-eyes?
Hirato...
(Trust)
I follow you around
tsukimatou
Did he do this on purpose?
(Trash)
It's over there
soko ni aru
What?!
Both the light and darkness
hikari mo yami mo
You really have a horrible personality.
tsunagari dasu
They begin to connect
Like puzzle pieces
piisu no you ni
Because there is a reason
riyuu ga aru kara
Hirato-san, the reason you pay so much attention to Gareki-kun is
because he was in that ship, isn't it?
Whether it happened by chance or by design
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
What ship?
That Kafka research lab ship.
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
Oh.
It was just the right timing for Gareki, who escaped death from that ship,
The temperature of my heart
kokoro no ondo ga
when he met Nai, who from that chance meeting, led Gareki all the way here.
Rises little by little
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
Something like a miraculous encounter, huh?
I'm just being myself
hontou no jibun no mama de
It feels like everything just mysteriously came together.
I want to tell you
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
It could be that Nai's very existence attracts the inevitable to happen..
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
Be my reason
Everything...
subete ga ima
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
By your side...
Be my reason
By your side
kimi no soba de
Be my power, future
See ya.
When things unfold naturally
arifureta tenkai nara
What's up?
I should just set my mind at ease
anshin te wake ja nai daro
Always giving my all to anything
kurikaesu kakugo no rensa
Can also make me stronger
tsuyoku mo nareru sa
(Cloud)
Don't turn away
sorasazu ni
Gareki, you have become warm!
(Crash)
Deceive yourself no longer
mou nani mo gomakasanaide
Huh?
Just accept it
uketorun da
It fits you perfectly
jibun ni niau
A future that will dazzle
mabushii mirai wo
Good-bye,
you dumb animal!
The brightness beyond your false pride
bukiyou na puraido sono saki no buraito
Show the way with your smile
mitsuketai egao wo terashite
We will surely
bokura wa kanarazu
Reach the place where you are
soko ni tadoritsuku yo
Don't do it on a whim, nor to ease your mind
kimagure ja nai kiyasume mo nai
sei ippai no ima wo hashire
Right now, just run with all your might
As you feel something from
kasanari au bekutoru ni
Our fates which overlap
imi wo kanjinagara
Be my reason
By your side
kimi no soba de
Be my power, future