色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
That's absurd!
Sorry, but please leave us alone.
I'm glad there's nothing wrong with you, Nai-chan.
Can I go where Karoku is?
At the moment, Hirato is having a meeting for the mission.
Wait just a little longer.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you.
Then, take a rest here first.
Yogi.
Score 12
The Niji's Promise
What does it mean to be “a child of the Second Ship”?
What?
That damned four-eyes asked me if I wanted to become one.
But I don't know what he means by that.
A child of the Second Ship...
In other words...
Um... sorry, I don't really know.
Karoku, please wait for me.
Like you say, I can't deny the
possibility of this being a trap.
Even if it is a trap, those guys who have kept their guard so tight,
have created an opening for us.
If we take the bait, we might be able to make some progress.
The mansion where an associate of Lindain Group had disappeared,
is the same mansion where Tsukumo was held captive.
According to Tsukumo's report,
the granddaughter of Palnedo, Erisyuka, was at that mansion.
We also have information that she's associated with Karoku
from Yanari, the son of the president of Lindain.
Moreover, Karoku was telling Nai to go to the Smoky Mansion.
If that's the case, we should report to the Consulate Tower and receive permiss–
We'll lose our leads if we wait.
It'd be too late by the time we get an approval.
If in fact it really is an S.O.S. from Karoku, if we ignore it,
the keys to uncovering the mystery behind Karoku and the birth of Nai,
together with the analysis of Karoku's notebook,
will forever disappear into darkness.
It would be frustrating to let all the data you've collected go to waste, right?
That's right. So, please help us out, Akari-chan.
We will send a small team to ambush them tomorrow.
Very well.
Just as we expected.
But, I have one condition:
You'll have to take me along.
It's possible that a portion of the data retrieved at
the site may not be brought back in its initial condition,
so I would definitely want you to come with us.
Didn't you come here to talk to me?
When will the assault on the Smoky Mansion commence?
I can't reveal details of a mission to a civilian
before it's announced.
Is that all?
I'm of no use to them anyway.
I can't remain here like this.
How long should I stay here?
Nai's been getting along with everyone just fine,
so there's no reason for me to be here anymore.
In other words, you wish to leave the ship?
I don't plan on staying here any longer
embarrassing myself and being a burden to everyone.
It's the first time I've felt that
not being able to feel proud of myself can be so annoying.
That's right.
All right. I understand.
I will work on fulfilling your request.
Sure.
Do you want to go to the Smoky Mansion?
What? Can I?
Then I'll go.
Make yourself useful.
Is he really leaving the Second Ship?
Our target, the property of Palnedo, the CEO of Gald Company, Smoky Mansion.
The mission is to rescue Karoku who's inside the building,
along with discovering and seizing of any evidence related to Kafka...
and detaining any key personnel related.
Confirm your roles in the mission.
Make your final preparations and stand by.
My goodness, you're pathetic to be scared of a mere injection.
It's not the injection, but Akari-sensei at close range that I'm scared of.
Excuse me, why did you come all the way here today?
I'm here in order to accompany the team to the Smoky Mansion.
Huh? You're coming with us?
With my presence, the chances of you guys surviving will increase remarkably,
but I won't be able to ease the injuries caused through emergency treatment.
So make sure you don't mess up.
No...
As we expected, there was a transmission to an unknown location from the Second Ship.
Were they jamming it?
Don't worry.
It was blocked completely.
Everyone, equip your bracelets.
Confirm that it's locked.
Hand in raised position.
Activation test.
Keep in mind of your partner's actions,
prepare to fight using your own intuition.
Karoku.
Nai.
There's someone named Karoku here, isn't there?
I'm his buddy.
He contacted me to rescue him
because he's being held captive.
What?
I'm sorry.
This kid begged me so profusely,
so I brought him here to satisfy his request.
Sorry, I haven't introduced myself.
I am from the National Defense Organization, Circus,
the Second Ship Fighter, Yogi.
There's no one like that here.
There must be some kind of mistake.
Of course you would say that.
But that's just a lie!
Karoku!
Hey you!
Hey!
I'm sorry, I'll bring him back right away!
Stop!
Contact the mansion!
When I first heard it, I was stunned how childish the plan was.
It's intentional.
If they pretend to be an innocent organization,
they would be hesitant to create any bloodshed
at the front gate which connects to the ordinary world.
What's the problem?
Yes, sir.
Well, some random guy said Karoku-sama had asked for help and then...
Don't panic.
There's no problem.
But find him,
and take care of things properly.
Circus...
I don't know what made them so confident to come here,
but this place can never be revealed by mere humans.
Let them enjoy guessing what's truly hiding inside the box.
It's the job of humans to use their imagination.
And ours, to create and make it a reality.
Gareki-kun!
We're flying up.
What's that thing you're looking at?
I stole it from the man at the front gate.
What? Back there?
I thought it might have a rough sketch of the premises.
Karoku!
Uro is asking you to return to your room.
Did something happen?
I'm not sure.
But I don't really care,
because I'm with you.
The skies roared and the wind has risen.
What?
It'll be raining soon, so let's go inside.
It appears that someone is here to see me.
Karoku?
My special child.
Good. I've disabled the main security system.
It should help to keep the guards off our backs for the time being.
Gareki-kun, you're amazing.
You're always studying by reading difficult books, aren't you?
Is it because... you want to go into that line of work in the future?
Well...
There's a job like that in Circus too...
What? "Studying," you say?
It just helps me get a living.
I've obtained control over the system.
I'll connect it to the Second Ship now.
Yogi.
Ah, okay.
First of all, this button...
No, the one below.
What?
Next, the right one.
Then, the one on the bottom left!
The side switch... lift it up!
The security's been turned off!
What the hell happened?!
We have complete control over the network.
Go.
We are the National Defense Organization, Circus.
Everyone, stay where you are and follow our orders.
Come, let's go treasure hunting.
With your ears, sift through the sounds of monsters and treasures being moved around.
If you can't find him, you may never see Gareki-kun again.
Why are you having so much trouble with a mere organization like Circus?!
They took control of the network.
Huh?
Our data's leaking out!
Gareki-kun, outside!
Let's see.
Since they're dancing for us, I should welcome them with applause.
With a rhythm so loud that it will never leave their ears.
I hear a loud sound.
The enemy has finally showed their true colors.
Here they come!
Everyone, to victory!
Gareki-kun!
Him again...
Are they trying to destroy the entire mansion?
We must hurry!
Kiichi, I'll leave you to take care of things here!
Okay!
Hey Kiharu, he's getting away!
I'll be your opponent!
The girls in Circus are all pretty cute, huh?
You'll realize that I'm much more than just cute!
Open up, Karoku! You're inside, aren't you?
Erisyuka-sama, we should be going soon.
No! I won't go unless Karoku is coming with me!
We can't stay! Circus is on their way here!
Circus?
It appears that someone is here to see me.
My special child.
So that girl is coming...
To see Karoku again?
Does she love Karoku?
No! I don't want that!
I won't allow them to meet!
Uro, that girl from Circus is coming for Karoku, right?
I'll never let them mee–
Crate of Thorns!
If he wasn't around,
I... would definitely have died!
I must listen closely!
Karoku had said he's here!
Oh, sorry I laughed at you.
But you were behaving just like a little animal...
Nai-kun, I'll become your eyes.
So close them and concentrate on listening.
Uro, don't let that girl and Karoku see each other!
Your wish is my command.
I'll toy with these women from Circus until they die.
Set your mind at rest.
Huh?
Greetings, lovely goddesses of Circus.
You're Uro-san, aren't you?
Thanks for personally coming to greet us.
It seems like a considerable amount of things have been removed from the building.
What's the present situation?
Let's see...
Everything has pretty much been neatly tidied up,
but we didn't come here for a cleaning inspection.
Well then, wha–
How admirable, you didn't dodge at all.
You're pretty well-trained, aren't you?
I'm right, aren't I?
Normal human beings wouldn't be able to avoid a Circus member's attack,
nor land on the ground unharmed after falling such a distance.
You're under arrest as a level 6 member of Kafka!
I'll be right back.
Hello. It's been a long time.
You know, right now Nai is coming to see me.
How would you like to come along?
As sparkling stars descend,
the little lamb learns of the sky.
The Second Ship Fighter of the National Defense Organization, Circus, Tsukumo!
As well as Iva!
Here we come!
Willfulness of the Constellations!
Die.
Sensei, exactly what do we achieve from doing this?
What the hell are you doing?!
Sensei...
The more I think about it, the more I don't understand.
Varuga are superior beings that threaten our very existence, are they not??
Even Circus members have a hard time dealing with them,
and have so far failed to suppress the activities of Kafka.
I couldn't stop trying to figure out why we've been losing,
even when we're supposedly doing things that are right.
It hurts so much thinking about it constantly.
I thought over, and over, and over again.
And it finally came to me...
I figured that they're strong because they're the ones on the right side of justice.
Azana!
We didn't notice that because we're inferior lifeforms to them.
We just couldn't see the truth.
We had lost sight of it!
Wh-What are you say–
Akari-sensei.
You possess wonderful capabilities.
They would certainly accept you as one of them.
Azana... You...
Joyful Blindness.
Jiki-kun...
Nai-kun, just focus.
Mr. Sheep!
Mr. Sheep! Mr. Sheep!
The sheep are just mere machines.
A new one can always be made.
We played together...
You wouldn't know if that's the same sheep, right?
There's so many of them, and every one of them looks the same.
But Jiki-kun...
Out of those I've met so far...
None of them had been the same.
Mr. Flower and the other Mr. Flower...
They were different.
If Karoku dies, it means he'll be gone forever.
I must find him.
Everyone...
The sky told me it was going to rain,
and the little ones told me that lots of flowers had bloomed.
That's right...
My voice will also reach far away!
Sapphire Crown!
I'm surprised that you've lasted this long.
I respect you for that.
But the difference between our abilities is far too great to begin with.
Is the Second Ship Captain hiding in his ship?
I can't believe he's just sitting back and watching the battle.
He should not only give instructions, but get his ass do–
What?!
Impossible! The gate shouldn't have been opened...
Banshees?
Our leader wishes to capture you alive.
I was having a really hard time holding back, you know?
What's that?
Preview
Gareki-kun, what's wrong?
Why are you letting out such a deep sigh as if you've lost all hope?
What happened? Tell me! Okay?
If you have any problems, tell me all about it.
Got it? Okay?
I'll definitely help you!
Can you shut up for a moment?!
How the hell can I talk like this?!
Score 13
Karneval
Okay? Okay?