色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Score 7
「The Mermaid's Sigh」 and
the Three Knights
Ever since that incident, Gareki-kun has been really depressed.
That's understandable.
She was like family to him; one week's just not enough time to cope with something like that.
I have an idea.
Nai-chan, Gareki-kun, you guys should come to the parade with us!
Um?
While it definitely takes time to recover from the loss of a loved one,
having an opportunity to take your mind off things helps too.
Sure, I'll go.
Wow.
Darn it.
Gareki, you look different.
What do you expect? I'm wearing different clothes.
What Nai-chan means to say is that your new look is cool.
At least, that's what I think.
Why do I have to come?
It's a pain in the neck.
Why are you guys having a show in the first place?
No one has conducted a full investigation.
We're supporting the First Ship this time.
Since we happen to be in the same town as them, they asked us to help out.
There'll be many stands to choose from.
It'll be fun.
Isn't that right, Tsukumo-chan?
By the way, Tsukumo-chan, why did you choose that costume?
Is something wrong?
Are you having fun, Gareki?
Sort of.
Yogi said something about Gareki losing his family.
I think “family” means someone you care about.
What does it mean to care about someone?
Watch where you're going.
I get upset seeing Gareki depressed.
Is this what it means to care about someone?
How does it happen?
I was really happy when Gareki saved me.
Gareki was saved by Tsubaki-san too,
and they became family because of the bond they share.
And kindness is the foundation of that bond, isn't it?
But have I ever been kind to others?
How can I fill that hole she left in his heart?
Karoku was also kind to me.
But still…
You'd better tell Gareki that you don't need him anymore.
Those words were scary.
Why would he say that?
I wonder where Karoku is right now.
And what should I do when I meet him?
Wow, the Circus is so cool!
No, we aren't really…
See, he has horns! Horns!
That's so cool!
Oh, oh, lemme touch 'em!
No, let me touch them!
Me, me!
Man, Gareki-kun, you're a big hit with the kids, huh?
Please!
Dammit. Get them away from me.
Everyone, I've got some candy bars over here!
Wow, candy bars!
All right, line up, everyone.
Hey, can I talk to you?
What's that, Kiichi-chan? What happened?
Our high-performance rabbit, which is under maintenance, just got lost in the parade.
I'll have you take care of it.
I'm sorry. I'm busy now.
Here are the candy bars!
It's an emergency!
Listen to me.
Its defense functions are malfunctioning. It could attack the children!
I'm a little busy right now.
The rabbit's too fast to be caught by the Security Force.
I'm the only one from the First Ship who could search for it.
I'll go.
What?
But you'll have to be on stage shortly, won't you?
Um… I'll go.
Iva-neesan.
I'll have to leave for a while.
Please take care of Nai-chan and Gareki-kun for me, okay?
Oh yeah!
Did she even hear me?
Now then, bye-bye perona!
You're already saying bye-bye perona?
Bye-bye pero… na.
Aren't you going to show us the “Sparkling Prince”?
You're leaving already?
Don't you like us?
Of course I do! But first I need to take care of some work with my other cat friends.
I… I'll give them candy bars.
Nai-chan, I'm thankful for your offer, but you won't fit in this costume.
Ah, Gareki-kun!
You're late!
I'm sorry.
What happened to your face?
Haha, I met with some… resistance.
Gareki? Where are you?
Yogi, Gareki disappeared!
What's wrong, Yogi?
Nyanperona! Welcome back!
Nyan-kichi.
Hey, have you shrunk?
Your legs are sagging.
Go higher! Higher!
Give us candy bars!
Please!
This must be today's best show.
Iva-san!
I can't find Gareki.
Don't worry about it.
Gareki-kun is delivering sweet dreams right beside us.
It's hard work, you know.
Damn it all!
Okay, we'll be rehearsing the last scene, the confession of love.
Please give it your best shot!
Start!
Please accept my devoted love for you.
Your beauty has stolen my heart away–
Excuse me, can you please…?
Is something wrong?
Jiki-kun, it's not like you to make mistakes.
No, it's not that. Tsukumo-chan, what's with that costume?
I'll wear the right costume during the real performance.
Please do so.
What's wrong?
It's nothing… I think.
I can't take it anymore. Where did that rabbit go?
It's not here, isn't it?
The rabbit has a red tag on its ear.
Are you even trying to look for it?
Why would I be here if I wasn't?
You might rank highly like I do, but you fail your missions pretty frequently!
I can't help but question your ability.
You're always mentioning rank,
but the scores we received on our recruitment exams mean nothing now.
Oh yes they do!
If you don't complete the mission properly, it makes me look bad!
Kiichi-chan, calm down!
Look at you! You hesitated because you sympathized with the opponent!
That, and you don't give it your all!
Kiichi-chan!
That kindness of yours makes me sick!
If you stop for one individual, you won't be able to protect everyone else!
You may be right about that, but… everyone else…?
Wait, that's it!
If the rabbit's defense functions are malfunctioning,
it'll probably go to a place with more  people to try and protect them!
The theater at the plaza!
I hope they found the rabbit.
Come in.
Tsukumo-chan, are you ready?
Thank you for helping the First Ship.
I'm more than happy to play the role of your lover.
That's an incorrect interpretation.
The story depicts the egoistic feelings of a young general.
He abducted a mermaid he was attracted to for his own selfish desires.
You shouldn't mistake the theme of this–
Well, yes! You're right.
Let's see, let me check the apparatus!
When I sit down on the bed, the bottom of the bottle you are in will open.
So, you should hide yourself amongst the bubbles and get out of the bottle that way.
The scene where the mermaid escapes from the sealed bottle will shock the audience.
That's the highlight of the play.
Let's do our best.
All right.
Filled with the power of a man's spirit,
I'm the Sparkling Prince who makes your hearts throb!
The drink I gave you earlier was a drug that'll turn you into a human.
I will not make you the King's gift.
When you become human, you will be mine on that bed tonight.
Such a nasty guy.
He has such leering eyes.
Please escape, mermaid princess!
I will now close the lid.
As a human, the longest you can remain underwater is a few minutes at most.
I hope you understand your only one choice lies with me.
I will wait for you on the bed.
The bottom of the bottle looks unsealed.
I think it's broken!
I'll seal it now.
Good work.
That bastard!
Ga-Gareki?
Ah… Yogi?
I'll kill him.
Tsukumo's show will be over soon, so you should rest now.
What? Tsukumo-chan?
Ah?
She's saying something.
Let's see…
What is it?
Is it your specialty, that super hearing power again?
Can't breathe… Can't open… No air...
What should I do?
If I break the glass, I might hurt the audience in the front row.
The water's…
Jiki-kun!
I'm tired of waiting.
I'll drag you out right now!
What? That rabbit–!
You're trying to break something.
You're a bad guy.
Huh? Something came out.
Is that thing helping the mermaid?
Is that the rabbit from the First Ship?
Could it be that malfunctioning rabbit?
That piece of shit!
This isn't good. If this goes on any longer…
The only place left is inside the theater!
Iva-neessan?
Can't you enter from under the apparatus?
It's sealed from the inside and we can't open it from here.
Iva-san!
Tsukumo-san is locked in the bottle on the stage!
Jiki-san is trying to break the bottle,
but the rabbit from the First Ship is preventing him from doing so!
I see.
All of you, act according to my instructions!
What?
B-But we don't even have scripts!
It hurts...
Everyone...
Serves you right, Jiki-sama.
I've decided to work with the rabbit and these people to punish you.
Iva-san?
Dammit.
Me? Oh, I'm so glad you're alive, our sweet little sister!
We became human in order to save you.
Our little sister!
Everyone, bow!
Come, return to the castle with your brothers.
Our little sister!
They're helping others.
They're good people.
It's time to wake up from this dream and go home.
I was worried for a moment there.
The curtains are still up.
What?
I'll punish you for dumping me and chasing a little girl like her!
Huh?
That bastard, he's two-timing?!
He's the enemy of all women!
What are you doing putting Tsukumo in danger?
Wait, Iva-san?
I will now show you the consequences of your actions.
I-Iva–!
You will address me as "my Queen"!
Go for it, nee-chan! Get him!
Tsukumo-chan, everyone, are you all okay?
Thank you.
I'm fine.
It's such a relief, isn't it?
When everything turns out okay, even incidents like these can be fun memories–
"Fun," my ass.
Now, how 'bout I teach you a lesson?
What? Why?
You already punched me once...
Wait!
You should be thanking me for going easy on you with a slap!
I'm so glad.
Huh?
The hell?
Gareki-kun has been so depressed lately.
I'm so happy that you've recovered enough to hit me.
I'm really glad that I got to march in the parade with you.
Dammit. You lost it or something?
How did you like your first parade?
Did you have fun?
Fun?! You shittin' me?! That was my last parade!
In the first place, what the hell's with this “Sparkling Prince”?
It's retarded!
The night has only just begun!
Let's all go out for a night on the town!
Jeez...
We would have been watching this in the front row.
It's all that doctor's fault.
We're working overtime because of him.
Shh! Formation Alpha!
Akari-sensei, you're such a hard worker!
But there was a show going on tonight. You must have received lots of invitations, right?
You must be a real ladies' man, huh?
I keep my distance from women.
Impressive!
Well, if you'll excuse me…
Huh?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
We couldn't watch the play because of you!
Don't you dare think all girls are shallow enough to fall for your looks, money, and power.
I really wish someone would shut Akari-sensei down hard!
At least let him suffer for once!
Oh, Akari-sensei!
Azana, what happened to your face?
It seems like I didn't try hard enough...
It seems quite attached to you, Sensei.
I haven't even shown it one ounce of kindness.
Well, here's the report…
There's nothing wrong with the food and ventilation.
The plants in the cage are fresh,
but it would feel more secure if there were a greater variety of plants....
in there to match its original environment.
Sensei, your report…
Why is it so attached to me?
It's impossible to understand.
What's that smell?
Smoked Taruneru.
Don't eat that here!
This place will reek for days.
It's been a long day, and I'm in no mood to see either of you.
My cells will die out with all the stress you cause me.
Your very existence is obstructing my daily activities.
You should work. Work yourselves to death!
Only when you collapse will I bring myself to look at the two of you.
You're just upset because you never take any breaks.
What's that?
Please sit down. We can't discuss things in a civil manner if you're standing.
This is my research laboratory!
All right, all right.
Let's just have a glass of wine.
I have no reason to drink with you!
Cheers!
You shouldn't have gotten him drunk.
You're the one who kept pouring him drinks.
And you're the one who encouraged him.
Now, how was it?
Well, you could say that ending the distribution route is an accomplishment.
But we still don't know where it came from.
So, can you go to Rinoll in my place?
Don't look at me like that!
Think of it as a vacation in the snow.
It'll be an easy investigation, you'll just be verifying a few things.
It's not that cold… it's just…
Well, it is kinda cold.
Every once in a while, it can be quite the vacation for the young ones.
It's so cold…
Let's finish up and head home right away.
Wait a sec.
Okay, I got the flag set up somewhere unexpected.
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
What's up with these pictures?
They're all photos of Tsukumo as a mermaid!
Well, I just happened to take them.
It seems I need to teach your body another lesson.
But the play's over, Iva-san.
Iva-san?
I mean, my Queen!
Score 8
Silvery Box