色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Hello... you must be tired after the long flight.
The mansion you'll be investigating in this fores–
Hi... Hi... Hirato-san, you idiot!
Thank you for helping out with the show.
From what I've heard, there were all kinds of blunders.
According to this report based on the surveys done by the citizens,
the nature of the play was questionable.
Nyanperona was acting out of character... and well,
these are just some of the examples cited.
Still, it's commendable that no one was injured.
Members of the First Ship would like to thank you guys.
I want you to go to Rinoll, the Ice Crystal Town.
"Have a break", while you carry out the additional investigations.
Consider it a reward.
What was that kind smile all about?!
Score 8
Silvery Box
A moment please.
This is something from the Second Ship's Captain.
Eh? Something from Hirato-san?
I wonder what's inside.
Huh? It's empty.
A snowman?
Snowman?
Yukkin, a warm snowman created by the design team at the Research Tower.
Yukkin?
Yukkin!
So... So cute!
It's so warm!
Hirato-san... Does he care about us or not?
I don't understand Hirato-san at all!
Seeing as to how he's letting us travel together, I suppose we're just going to be bait again.
I'm not satisfied with just smelling the smoke.
That idiot hiding within the smoke, basking in his sense of superiority as he watches people cry...
If this can allow me to seize him by the collar, I'll play along and let them use me.
Sorry, Gareki-kun.
What?
You were feeling cold, weren't you?
You were blowing in your hands, Gareki.
I don't need a snowman.
Let the girl and brat hold it.
I'm older than Gareki by a year, so you don't have to hold back.
Just let Nai hold on to it, will you!
Ga-Gareki-kun... It's wrong! You're using it wrong! It hurts...
Well then, I'll be on standby back at the lodging.
Ga-Gareki.
I strongly question your decision to let him move around so freely.
There are a few known examples of captured Niji,
believed to be the same kind of species that Nai is formed from, because of its rare existence.
All experiments in breeding them have failed.
Since sounds in their natural environment are related to sustaining their lives,
we presume that being kept in a closed area creates large amounts of stress on it.
For this reason, I feel that the current situation is the best way to supervise Nai.
We received a report that he was almost abducted by Kafka!
The Research Tower and Circus have different objectives in handling Nai.
The Research Tower views him as an important specimen to advance technology.
But for us, he's a mysterious dancer who's able to bring Varuga to us.
I hope you understand that the encounters with Varuga and the dangers associated with them
are part of the role that we imposed on him.
I believe that you worry that if he's taken away, there will be disadvantages...
If that ever happens,
I'll kill him with my own hands.
Wait, Hirato!
You're right about Nai's value as only an experiment specimen to me.
But taking a life is not something you should decide at your own convenience.
You're such a saint.
What do you mean?
You belong to those that protect lives,
and I to those that take them away.
A difference of opinions between us is inevitable.
The phrase “feigned politeness” exists for someone like you.
Hey, hey, you guys are really…
Who do you think you're talking to, Tsukitachi?
Compared to Hirato's feigned politeness, you're just plain rude!
Please don't take it out on me, Akari-chan.
I'll excuse myself then, Akari-san.
Well, he may come off hard-headed, but he's actually quite kind-hearted on the inside.
I don't believe he wants to kill Nai.
Think about what he said earlier.
I don't think the higher-ups were too happy about it.
"What a short-sighted idea. To think that killing him would solve everything".
It's more beneficial to keep Nai alive.
"Therefore I think we should hold back the opinion to dissect Nai".
"I suppose those opinions to dissect him began surfacing because they were having...
a hard time decoding Karoku's notebook".
Don't worry.
Someone's always following Nai.
Besides, we've also attached a transmitter to his bracelet.
Let's go.
Yukkin, this way.
Yukki. Yukki. Yu.
Love.
He's such an idiot.
This mansion somehow gives me the creeps.
Well, this vacation house is owned by an executive officer
of a Kafka-related company, which the First Ship busted.
What exactly are we looking for?
To confirm if anything was left out of the search when this place was busted.
It's just a follow-up to check things out.
To see if there are still documents or drugs remaining that are related to Kafka.
Nai-chan, aren't you cold?
Huh?
I'm sorry. Hirato-san was probably thinking that you could play with the snow
once the blizzard was gone.
Snow is fun.
It was so fluffy and squishy.
It was lots of fun, right?
Really?
Yeah. The feeling of my feet sinking was new to me.
By any chance, was this Gareki-kun's first time experiencing snow?
He was saying those words unconsciously, wasn't he?
That's so adorable.
All right! Let's work hard and spend the last day playing!
Yay!
In the end, there was nothing there.
It's not really a bad thing that we didn't find anything.
Yukkin is gone.
Yukki. Yukki. Yukki. Yu-
Hey, there really is something here.
What? Did you find a rare item?
Yu…Yu…Yukki.
I'm going back to the mansion, so everyone else should head back to the lodging–
Nai, listen carefully for that snowman's voice.
It's already going to be difficult to hear its voice,
because the snow muffles sound.
Sure, I'll do my best.
Yogi, let's hurry.
Okay, Tsukumo-chan.
Awesome! It's so warm!
At this rate, we can play with it for two more hours.
This is an item from the Second Ship of Circus.
I've never seen this before so it must be a rare item.
Then that means Circus is here.
Yahoo!
Aren't we competent for getting rid of all of the evidence just before they came?
We covered everything up. Right, Kiharu?
It's amazing! Magnificent! Gorgeous!
If there is anything we missed, Uro-san will kill us.
Let's just kill Circus with our momentum!
Don't get so excited.
It's such a pain.
But, if I can get some limited-edition Circus items, I'm game.
Shall we do it?
A sound?
I wonder if he fell into this hole.
I'll go take a look.
Yogi, I'll go too.
Right, lend me your ears, Nai-chan.
Be careful.
I can't see very well in this darkness, but it seems to be man-made.
Yukkin! Are you here?
I hear sounds from over there.
Gareki-kun?
Owwww. I'm sorry, Gareki-kun.
Tsukumo-chan, stay there in case of an emergency.
This is a man-made hole.
There's a door.
This place is under the mansion, isn't it?
Right.
You two stay behind me, since I can't tell what will happen.
There it is!
It hurts! Dammit!
It's there. I don't want to go anymore. Let's go home.
You idiot, look carefully. It's just a doll.
Hey, Nai-chan, wait!
Don't touch it!
Stop it!
The box... something's shaking inside?
Yukkin.
Yukkin!
I'm so glad.
Where have you been?
Yuukkin.
We were all looking for you.
Look, that girl is a member of Circus.
Of course. She was looking into the hole where we found that white dango.
It's so obvious, Kagiri-san.
You're an idiot, Kiharu.
If she was just an ordinarily person, we would've broken the promise with Uro-san
to not attract attention to ourselves.
Then it'll be bad even if we encounter members of Circus, right?
But Kiharu, we're going to kill her, aren't we?
In that case, we'll make sure even the dead can't talk. We'll be commended for killing Circus.
I couldn't sense him approaching.
Could he be?
Tsukumo-chan, sorry for keeping you waiting!
Kiharu.
She had companions!
Yogi!
Are you two okay?
Yes.
Mm-hm.
Something must've happened above.
I have to save Tsukumo-chan!
Wait.
Don't waste your energy.
Wha–? Why are you carrying such a thing?
I found them at the mansion.
So what? You took them? You don't call that–
Let's go back to that doll room.
Tsukumo-chan!
Yogi, that was…
Sorry to surprise you.
Gareki-kun made a bomb out of things we found underground.
Hey, don't ignore us!
Varuga!
Tsukumo-chan.
Nai-kun.
It hurts!
Come on this way. You're so lame.
Wai– Look at the clothes the black-haired guy's wearing.
The special thermal coats that only the Research Tower personnel wear!
Tsukumo-chan, take Nai-chan somewhere safe.
It's not in my collection!
But…
A super rare item!
Take care of him until we group up with you later.
Are they after Nai-chan again?
Gareki-kun, I'll protect you, so do as I say...
Hey you, stop standing in front of me!
You're getting in my way!
Hey, I'm protecting you!
I'm a member of Circus, and you're just a normal boy, get it?
This is my duty.
Not only that, I don't want my friend to get hurt...
Come again?
Your friend?
In what way?
He's dead serious!
W-Well,
I see... Am I the only one to think that?
Come to think of it, I don't recall Gareki-kun ever calling me by my name..
What? Maybe he dislikes me?
Hey, I'm old enough to tell the difference between our abilities to fight.
But I'm not useless either.
Wha– You're right. I'm sorry.
I'll provide you with support.
Do your best.
Okay, sure!
Filled with the power of man's spirit.
I'm the Sparkling Prince who makes your hearts throb!
The Second Ship Fighter of the National Defense Organization, Circus, Yogi.
Let's fight!
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
No, it's not Tsukumo-chan's fault.
Thanks for saving me just now.
I was very happy.
But you mustn't get hurt, Nai-kun.
I was so scared that you may have been hurt badly.
I… I want to be strong like you, Tsukumo-chan.
Can I be strong?
Nai-kun, you have a very strong soul.
You've gone through so much, yet you've never been discouraged.
I think it's great that you can be kind to others at all times.
I feel relaxed when I'm with you, Nai-kun.
I'm sure everyone, including Karoku-san, feels the same way.
So let us return home safely.
Because you're telling me not to damage the black-haired boy's clothes,
I can't go all out.
Hold it– Shouldn't we kill the ones that got away?
There's nothing interesting about those two!
However, this encounter gives us better items!
They're not after Nai-chan?
Hey, what kind of person is your boss?
Come again?
I'm asking you what kind of person he is.
Ah, I see.
It's understandable that Gareki-kun doesn't like me.
I couldn't save Yotaka-kun.
Are you talking about our boss, Uro-san?
He'll get pissed at me if he sees us fighting so pathetically...
Say, can I go on a rampage?
I give up. You're such a pain in the neck.
It's time for the real fight.
Let's show them our true powers!
Rasudan Bug!
You lost your eyesight temporarily due to the special rhythm of light signals
being transmitted to your brain.
Hey, handsome lil' guy!
Gareki-kun, say something–
Yogi–
Hey, be quiet.
Gareki-kun, where are you?!
Oh? Why, I haven't dealt the finishing blow yet...
Ga..re...
I can finally see–
Let's do something fun. Something awesome...
I'll be very happy if everyone laughs as if they're screaming.
Yogi!
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Tsukumo-senpai, will you be transferred to Rinoll?
I will be conducting an investigation over there.
Please don't forget about me.
It'll only be for a short time, so I won't forget you.
I'm so very sad.
Score 9
Blue Rose
Thank you, Kiichi-chan.