色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Nevertheless, I'm quite surprised that such beautiful and young people are members of Circus.
Hearing that from a person who's in charge of the Lindain Group at the young age of 42 years old...
I'm not sure if I should be glad.
But that is my honest impression.
Well then, how may we be of help?
To be frank with you,
it appears that some companies associated with the Gardo Corporation are harboring monsters.
Score 11
Ice Cream Parade
Here's the Walking Iron Castle, Vantam.
It's our long-awaited day off, so let's make the best of it!
Nai-chan, where do you want to go?
Well, let's see…
Say…
Where? Jiki-kun?
I'll go off on my own.
What? Come on, let's go together!
There are a few shops I'd like to check out.
Hey, Jiki-kun!
Next: my number-one recommended shop!
Here it is!
Wow!
We're not going in here.
Huh? What? But Nai-chan looks
like he's having fun!
You should enjoy yourself here too, Gareki-kun!
Stop it. That's enough. Shut up...
There are so many Nyanperona goods here!
Shut up... You've gotta be kidding me!
Damn you.
Who gives a shit about Nyanperona?!
It's just a stupid character costume to dress up in!
I have absolutely no interest in that crap!
Wh-Why are you lying, Gareki-kun?
Nyanperona is alive and doing just fine!
He is in no way just a character costume!
You shouldn't have said all that, Gareki-kun.
Hey!
Ah, well, Nyanperona really exists, you know!
The last 3 digits of your card number, Z-Z-A.
This is the undisclosed exclusive code for the National Defense Organization.
Also, from what you just said a second ago,
it's obvious that you're the one in the Nyanperona getup!
Nyanperona is alive... You're ruining the children's dreams!
What do you want, brat?
Don't call me a brat!
I'm Yanari.
Yanari…-kun?
I'm looking for a pasta shop with a blue roof and a black gate.
If you don't want me to expose the secret of Nyanperona,
find that pasta shop for me!
Even though it's the same type of soil, there are subtle differences.
It's much the same with seedlings and soils; you've got to examine them carefully before buying.
And speaking of examining, those uniforms aren't half-bad...
Excuse me.
Azana, every time I see you, you seem to have more cuts.
It would appear that nothing unusual has happened at Vinto since then.
Right. Also, the poachers' organization has been busted.
That's wonderful news.
Hirato-san was here, wasn't he?
Yeah, he was. So?
Oh, right, you two don't get along.
Well, I was wondering if he found any clues.
I don't blame you for being suspicious,
but there's no traitor in the Research Tower.
We don't know the identity of the person who
pretended to be your subordinate at Vinto.
But it's true that information is leaking.
No, he doesn't seem to have found anything yet.
There's no evidence, but the rate at which they replace their employees is abnormal.
What's even more interesting, people who have left the companies...
soon mysteriously died from sickness, got killed in accidents, or went missing.
This isn't known to the public, but there was...
a party held by Mr. Palnedo at an establishment owned by Gardo Corporation.
My acquaintance, who was invited to that party, has gone missing.
I see.
That place is no longer one for the living, is it?
Filled with the power of man's spirit.
Ba-zing!
I'm the Sparkling Prince who makes your hearts throb.
The Second Ship Fighter of the National Defense Organization, Circus, Yog– Nyanperona
...is here!
For some reason, he doesn't look that attractive when he's not in the Nyanperona costume.
I only did it because you asked me to.
Someone is watching us.
Why are you staring at us?
Take off that head and show your face.
I... I...
Stop, Gareki-kun!
What do you think you're doing in front of the children?!
Their dreams are important!
I'm... I'm Rissun!
You're a mascot of Vantam, aren't you?
I'm the guide for this city!
Then, do you know the pasta shop with a blue roof and a black gate?
My friend wants to go there.
We couldn't find it even after searching for it online.
Oh, if that's what you're looking for, it should be in area E-22.
Really?
Please have a memorable day with your friend!
Thank you, Rissun-san!
Nai, you said that I was your friend earlier.
How did we become friends?
How?
How do you recognize someone as a friend?
I don't know.
What?
But...
Um, well... it happens when you start to feel all warm inside.
Fool!
I told you to keep an eye on him!
What are you going to do if he becomes a target again?!
What seems to be the trouble?
Oh, it seems that my son sneaked out of his room.
My subordinates are currently somewhere in the city,
I'll have them look for him, just in case.
An emergency order?
Locate a nine-year-old boy.
The son of the president of Lindain Group?
Bluish-black hair…
Wearing a blazer and a pair of breeches.
Name is Yanari.
Isn't that…
Rissun-san!
Did you follow us?
A-Ahem.
Your voice... Who are you?
What? No!
Don't move!
What do you think you're doing?
Using that costume... you disgust me.
Don't move!
We've been looking for you, Yanari-sama!
Are you okay?
Come, this way please.
N-No!
I'm not going home yet!
I still have something I need to do!
Yanari-kun has somewhere he wants to go.
Let us, Circus, take care of these scoundrels.
Hirato-san?
The blondie is trying to escape with the boy.
Go after him.
Huh? What?
Oh!
Hirato-san let us escape.
What a nice guy!
Is this the pasta shop?
No, it's not.
But this is the right place.
I can finally see my mother.
Mother?
Mother!
Yanari...-san?
She passed away due to an accident a month ago.
Sorry, we couldn't inform you of the funeral
because we didn't have any means of contacting you.
No, I should be the one apologizing.
Thank you...
Yogi, Yanari-kun is hurting a lot inside, but I…
Well, ah..
What is it, Nai?
Yanari-kun.
Don't surprise me like that.
Why am I the one getting tied up?
For not only breaking the hearts of the children in the city,
but also exposing our children to danger.
Is that so?
I think Yogi is pretty flexible.
What are you talking about?
I meant Nai and you.
What? Why are you calling me your kid?
What are you smiling about?!
It's nothing.
Then, Gareki, would you like to become one of the children of the Second Ship?
Come again?
When my mother left the house because she'd had enough of my father's work,
I thought she abandoned me.
I secretly asked someone to take me to see her.
But when she looked at me, I ignored her.
I did an awful thing.
I'm such a horrible person!
Yanari-kun, that's not true.
Yes, it is!
That's why I haven't been able to make any friends!
Because my father does bad things in his line of work,
he's disliked by many people.
I'll probably end up becoming just like him!
No, I've already become like him.
And so I'll become worse, and worse, and worse,
until I'm as bad as it gets!
That's not something you should be telling yourself.
You're feeling hurt because you hurt your mother.
That makes you a kind person, Yanari-kun.
No matter where you are, you can be strong while maintaining that pure heart of yours.
As long as you stand firmly in what you believe.
Also, you already have friends, don't you?
Us.
Gareki-kun, who isn't here right now... even Tsukumo, who's outside – all of us are your friends.
Excuse me.
I made that for my mother.
Yanari. It's your birthday.
Happy birthday.
How are you? Have you grown?
Yanari, I'm sorry.
Yanari, I love you.
You know... When I'm Nyanperona,
whenever I meet children and spend time with them, even for a short time,
I feel that we are binded by fate.
Fate?
That's why, Nai-chan, we should properly bid him farewell.
Nai, thank you.
When you held my hand, I felt so relieved.
Thank you!
Gareki and Yogi did that for me.
And Karoku too.
Karoku?
I'm looking for Karoku.
That name... I think I've heard it somewhere before.
Yanari-kun, we should be leaving.
Yogi, Nyanperona is cool because you're in it.
R-Really?
Gareki, you weren't too bad when you fought with that fake Rissun.
You brat.
Nai, I bought this for my mother.
Use it.
You're my very first friend.
Yes.
Today was an extremely memorable day for me.
Would you like to become one of the children of the Second Ship?
What's that supposed to mean?
Shitty four-eyes.
I don't understand him at all.
Nai-chan.
Call for you.
A call?
Hello, is it Nai?
Yanari-kun?
The name of the person Karoku, whom you're looking for...
Eh?
It was mentioned by a girl in the selection school I was attending.
As I recall, her name is Erisyuka.
Erisyuka?
Does that mean I'll be working for the ship?
I've been with Nai because I thought he would bring me money.
I was going to take advantage of all that I could.
That's why I'm here.
But...
Since when did things that felt so normal to me make me feel so suffocated?
Gareki, I brought you a cup of juice.
Thank you.
I don't want to stand beside them feeling this way.
I can't stay here if I remain like this.
Let's talk, Nai.
Come down.
Nai!
Nai, you're late.
Karoku, where are you?
You didn't want to say good-bye to your friends?
That's so nice of you. But I can't see you yet, Nai.
Why did you leave me?
I was forcefully taken away.
Karoku, where have you been taken away to?
Tell me!
I'll try my best to find you!
Then... come right away.
I'll be killed before long.
My location is...
Nai-kun, are you okay?
He's at... the Smoky Mansion...
The Smoky Mansion?
Karoku is there.
Tsukumo-chan, I'll go to the Smoky Mansion.
Karoku… Karoku will be killed.
That place is difficult to get close to.
The Smoky Mansion is one of Kafka's main research institutions.
I hear that there hasn't been enough evidence to raid the place so far.
If you approach it carelessly, all our efforts thus far will be for naught.
Unless you have concrete evidence,
the higher-ups will not allow us to go there.
Erisyuka, the granddaughter of Palnedo, has connections with Karoku, right?
It would be tough to present the memories of Yanari-kun alone as evidence.
I'm going, no matter what.
What can you do even if you go?
I have to! Otherwise, Karoku will be killed!
Nai-chan...
Karoku said to "come right away."
So if I have to, I'll go alone.
I'll go.
I'm not a member of Circus,
so it'd just be considered trespassing even if I'm caught.
And if we can find some evidence, you guys would be able to act, wouldn't you?
What if something happens to you?!
In that case, I'll leave my ID behind and go!
I'll go too.
Hirato-san.
I...
Calm down.
You may go.
I'll take full responsibility.
Under the pretext of saving Karoku, we'll assault the target.
We'll take them on as Circus.
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Each one of us is different.
Long ears, eye color, voice, behavior and clothes... all of them are exactly the same, aren't they?
Take a good look at us. You will soon see the difference.
Don't you rabbits all say the same thing? You wanna bet?
Score 12
The Niji's Promise