She's in a state of clinical death.
Hi...ra...
I'm sorry for the disturbance this may have caused.
I am the Second Ship Captain of the National Defense Organization, Circus.
Hirato.
I'll come back at a later time to make an apology.
We'll be going now.
Circus...
色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Yukki.
Yukkin. Yukkin.
Yukkin. Yukkin. Yukkin.
Score 10
Tears of the Beast Handler
We need to register your voice,
so say something, anything you want.
He-Hello.
I'm coming in.
Making people say “I'm home,” must be Yogi's taste.
Voice registration has been completed.
Welcome to the First Ship of Circus.
First of all, you two will make sure this room is spotless.
Make sure to finish by my return.
I'm sorry if you were expecting to be treated as guests.
The Second Ship is full of idiots,
so maybe this job's too hard for you.
Gareki?
I'll finish it instantly.
It'll be fun to see if you can finish it by the time I come back.
Kii-chan is putting in a lot of effort into this.
It would be easier if we just left them alone.
We know pretty much everything about Nai.
As for him... He doesn't have a family register, huh?
Blood relatives are unknown.
And he was abandoned at Karasuna, too?
He was on a human trafficking ship that ran aground?
Isn't this the incident Tsukitachi-san and Hirato-san took care of?
Damn it.
There is no end.
What's wrong?
Because I've been working outside for a while, I got furballs.
Huh? Aren't you a high performance rabbit?
Can't you program yourself not to get furballs?
I'll brush you.
Thank you, Usa.
It feels nice, Usa.
Did he already forget that the cleaning for this room isn't finished yet?
What?
I give up.
I guess I've lost this match to that girl.
Okay, everyone come here.
What?!
Hi, Kiichi-chan. We'll be done in a minute.
Why are the rabbits helping you?!
Sorry, did I take too long?
Hey, I'm back.
They found Tsukumo-chan?!
Aren't you glad?
Hurrah! Hurrah!
Well, Yogi's still fast asleep so you two will have to stay here a little longer.
If you have any questions, I'll answer anything you want to know.
Is Tsubame–How is she?
She's doing just fine.
And she's always worrying about you, Gareki.
There's no need for her to worry about me.
Since she is under the protection of Circus, her movements are restricted.
But in return, we'll take care of Tsubame's grandfather.
What?
She was also happy by the fact that now she doesn't have to burden...
the benefactor who's been paying her hospital fees.
I see. I'm glad for the old man too.
Ga–
Speaking of which, what's the mechanism behind your weapons?
Oh, are you interested, kiddo?
Then how about we go and take a look for ourselves tomorrow!
What?!
Why are you inviting random people for no reason?
There's indeed a reason.
It's the place where the Circus bracelet, the very source of our powers, originates from!
We haven't even been able to lock down on our enemies yet.
What if something goes wrong?
There's no danger since all of us will be with them.
Right, Kiichi?
Of course.
I, Kiichi, am different from gofers of the Second Ship.
Let's eat.
We'll be having a field trip tomorrow.
Did you really just say field trip?
Just how the hell do you view your job, you idiot!
I'm sorry for bringing you here.
But it'll be the first time we do things together
I want to see how you two react.
Can you try running away from me without being caught?
Sure.
He was blown away by the rabbit back then, wasn't he?
Then let's start.
Up until now, the enemy hasn't show his true colors.
If they were to get serious, you'd die in a second.
This isn't a place where you can survive by going along or being friendly.
To put it bluntly, Gareki-kun, aren't you just a sacrificial pawn used to maintain
Nai-kun in a stable condition?
You should stop going along with dirty grown-ups,
and instead return to where you belong.
Well then, let's have fun tomorrow.
Let's enjoy tomorrow.
Where are you going?
Ah?
You wanted to talk to Jiki?
Did he say something?
Tsukitachi-san.
Yes?
I... don't want Gareki a sacrifice.
What? Oh, I see.
Let's try rephrasing what you just said.
Um...
Everyone gets into danger because I'm with them. But...
Nai, you think everyone gets hurt because of you?
Yes.
But it's also because you agreed to stay with Circus that
the Varuga whom we want to catch are drawn to us,
so you're helping us out a lot.
You should take advantage of the situation and use us to help find Karoku.
Even if something were to happen, we should all overcome it together.
No one will blame you.
Well, I had asked Gareki to come along with me.
That's why he often gets into danger.
If we part ways, Gareki can go home...
Nai, where do you want to go back to?
What?
I wonder where Gareki wants to go back to.
Both of you are involved with Varuga,
so it may be hard to fulfill your wishes.
Though,
don't you and Gareki have dreams in your heart?
Dreams in our hearts?
Choose the best thing you can do now in order to get a step closer to your dream.
If you care for others, don't just feel guilty but get to know their dreams.
No! Stop, please stop!
Sorry, but I’m in a hurry.
Just make up some kind of excuse to Akari-sens–
Go back to sleep!
Akari-sensei.
But! I can't bear the thought of Gareki-kun and Nai-chan having gone to the First Ship.
I'm sure they're being bullied!
Members of the First Ship have left for that investigation yesterday.
You mean to Vinto?
It appears that Nai and Gareki have gone with them.
I'm sure they'll get along just like you guys did.
Vinto is a government wildlife sanctuary that protects rare and unique creatures.
However, many animals are being poached and also the bodies of poachers have been found…
There's no use in explaining to them, since they won't understand anyway.
Hey, both of you, try not to get in our way.
Ah, you are…
I'm Azana from the Life Division.
It's been quite a while since Rinoll.
How'd you get hurt?
Well, they were inflicted by animals who tend to show their affection by playing with me...
We don't need any chit-chat.
Let's just get on to the investigation.
To work more effectively, let's split into two groups.
Personnel from Life Division, please lead the way.
Do you want to come with me, Gareki?
I'll tell you about that source of our powers.
I'll go.
Me too.
Nai-kun, shall we go?
Jiki-kun, you forgot your guide.
I'm fine with ignoring other people, but when it's the opposite it pisses me off.
Ever since the bodies of poachers were discovered,
the number of animals being killed have decreased.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
This one in particular was badly hurt by a poacher.
What happened to that poacher?
I heard he died.
Who found him?
Murano-senpai and I did.
I see.
I'm glad the animal survived.
Are you okay?
Were you able to sleep last night?
I'm fine.
Circus bracelets are made using the cells of the creatures here.
This is a severe environment with limited sunlight and food.
Creatures here have managed to evolve themselves in order to survive the harsh conditions.
They focused their evolution in high energy production and regenerative capabilities.
We extracted such cells, and through research, we came up with...
Incura, the omnipotent cell.
This is the cell that's embedded into our bracelets and enables our powers to materialize.
Go.
Are those also what you call "materializing"?
Yes. But it's also a double-edged sword.
What?
Manipulating the Incura cell isn't something that simple
If you release its power completely without any control,
you'll be overwhelmed by it.
Well, members of Circus are selected from people who have the capability to handle such power
and have gone through rigorous training.
Bodies of poachers were found around here.
Looking at the situation, I think we can conclude the culprits were Varuga, right?
So it's really done by Varuga?
According to the report, targets were limited to poachers.
Jiki-kun, I heard something coming.
It's just a moss lizard.
That's not what I heard.
What?
Murano-senpai!
Kiri, these people are not poachers!
It's this creature.
It's wary of humans,
because it had been attacked by a poacher.
This is bad. Kiri, calm down!
Kiri...
Stop!
Kiri has done nothing wrong!
I know. That's exactly why what you did was an act of great sin.
You're one of us brought together by the same mission,
but I can't give you special treatment.
Run, Kiri!
So they've hit the jackpot, huh?
What do you mean by "jackpot"?
Nothing to worry about.
Kiichi and Jiki are with Nai.
Kiri!
Oh no!
Yogi!
Gather!
Kiri!
Nai-chan, are you okay?
Yeah.
What should I have done?
If I hadn't given that drug to Kiri that time, he would've been dead.
I was so scared of losing Kiri that I didn't care if the drug would make him lose control.
I wanted to have such capabilities
to be able to protect everyone I care for.
Tell me how you obtained that drug.
I don't know his name.
But he claimed to work for Akari-sensei, so I trusted him.
That's so vague.
Well, I guess that's okay for now.
We'll have plenty of time for the interrogation.
No way! All Senpai wanted was to protect animals...
Jiki-kun...
Yogi...
I'll end your misery soon.
Your sacrifice will not be in vain.
My sickle will surely reach the evil within you.
Kiichi-chan...
Ah, Yogi...
Gareki-kun!
You called my name for the first time, didn't you?
What?
I'm so glad!
You've never called my name so I had thought you really hated me.
What are you talking about?
It's not the first time, right? Well, not that I ever really thought about this consciously...
No, never!
Yes, I did!
It's just you weren't listening!
At Rinoll, when you were unconscious...
I'm really sorry about what happened at Rinoll.
Are you physically okay?
I'm fine now.
Let's go back together to the warmth of the Second Ship!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Gareki-kun,
what's wrong?
You should be saying "I'm home," right?
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Tsukumo-chan!
Jiki-kun? Why are you here?
I have orders to stay with Nai-kun and Gareki-kun for the time being.
I look forward to it.
Is he okay?
Huh?
Oh, yes.
That's good. Thank you.
It's such a pain in the neck.
When I see him, I feel like my luck would go down.
Karoku-sama's condition seems to be pretty stable these days.
He'll eventually become just bones and skin anyway.
It's such a waste to give him food.
I want Gareki to tell me something.
What?
Where do you want to go back to?
Come again?
Where? Where?
Where? Where? Where?
Shut up!
I don't have such a place!
I froze for a moment just now.
I thought he saw right through me.
I know damn well that there's nothing much I can do!
But I wanted to change. I wanted to go out there and prove myself.
But in the end, what did I achieve?
Place I want to go back to?
I don't have such a place, nor would I have the right to go there!
You should be saying "I'm home," right?
But I want to stay here little longer.
Gareki, I want to stay where everyone is.
And, I'll be happy if I can find Karoku safe and sound.
So to make that happen, I'll do a lot of things.
Your words don't make any sense.
I see... So Yogi has evolved into such a simple form.
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
The room's all cleaned up so there's no problem, right?
mee!
It's not fair to use the rabbits!
That reminds me: I have these eclairs that you love so much.
ko
ru
n
Da
mee!
Hurray! I'll have them!
Da
ru
ma
sa
Jiki, where are you?
mee!
Jiki-kun's not around so I'll eat his share!
Score 11
Ice Cream Parade