色採々の音をつらぬいて
irotoridori no oto wo tsuranuite
Penetrating through colorful tones of music
身体が放つ美味なる温度
karada ga hanatsu bimi naru ondo
My body emits an alluring warmth
夜の訪れを待つ花のように
yoru no otozure wo matsu hanano youni
Like a flower awaiting the embrace of nightfall
光を畏れてる
hikari wo osoreteru
It shines away from the light
回れ消えゆくまで
maware kieteyuku made
Revolve until it disappears
その身を焦がす全て
sono mi wo kogasu subete
Expose with grace
さらけ出せ　しなやかに
sarakedase shinayaka ni
All that consumes my body with passion
雫は見つめる
shizuku wa mitsumeru
The teardrops are watching
愛を聴かせるための
ai wo kikaseru tameno
Even though I know the words
言葉を知ってるのに
kotoba wo shitteru noni
to make you listen to love
愛を語る為の言葉はない
ai wo kataru tame no kotoba wa nai
I do not have words to speak of my love.
泣き濡れて震えたって
nakinurete furuetatte
Even trembling with the tears
はるか遠い素顔は
haruka tooi sugao wa
The real face I once had
恋い焦がれるぬくもりのストーリー
koi kogareru nukumori no sutoorii
Tells the story of my burning love
その耳に残るのは
sono mimi ni nokoru nowa
The pieces of echoes that are left in my ears are
偏愛の輪舞曲（ロンド）
henai no rondo
The Rondo of Passion
Yotaka.
Are you...
I'm... hungry.
Score 5
Clown Prescription
Gareki-kun.
Take Nai-chan and leave the village right away.
Are you kidding?!
I need to talk to Yotaka!
He's in no state to talk right now.
Listen to me before you get yourself killed.
He's moving.
Let's meet up at Karasuna.
I can't go with you, sorry.
See you later.
Damn it.
What does he mean by "Listen to him"?
Don't screw with me!
I won't listen to you!
They're my...
If you don't have a name... How about "Gareki"? It means gravels of flower.
How do you like it?
It's nice, isn't it?
We're family.
Nonsense. It's worthless.
Here.
What?
Grandpa told me to bring you the scraps from the factory.
You're... always fiddling with something.
Hey, aren't you coming to dinner?
We're waiting for you Gareki.
What?
Are we supposed to eat meals together?
There he is! I found Gareki!
What do you want?
Want? Well...
I've been wondering where you were...
So, um...
Tsubame's been bugging me about where you've been, so...
Gareki.
Why are you here?
There's no way I could bring Tsubame to such a dangerous place, right?
So I was right.
A gun? Why do you have such a thing?
What the hell have you been doing?
It's none of your business.
Answer me!
Why are you still trying to act as if you're my brother?
How long do you think it's been since I left your place?
You asked what I'm doing?
I'm doing the kind of things that would kill dorks like you and Tsubame if you got involved.
Never come here again.
You idiot.
Go to hell!
Stay away from me.
Don't get involved with me.
I only deal with three kinds of people.
Scum, prey, and enemies.
They're harvested
from the field.
Hope you enjoy them.
Are they stupid or something? Honestly...
Nai, go back by yourself.
What?
This was the way we came.
If you go straight, you'll return to Karasuna.
Got it?
I'll lend this to you, so try not to stand out.
No way!
I don't want to go! No!
Hey–
what's the matter?
That thing was scary.
That's why I'm telling you to put on the hood and run away from here.
That's not what I mean.
I don't want Gareki to get broken up into pieces,
so I'll go with you!
Hey... Stop saying such damned things.
If there's anyone you should worry about, it should be
Yogi, who's gone to where Yotaka is, shouldn't it?
Yogi's strong.
Then are you saying that I'm weak?
You stupid animal!
What can you do if you come with me?!
Listen, Nai.
Your goal is to meet Karoku, isn't it?
You should remain calm and not get involved with unnecessary things like this.
Make use of Circus to reach your goal.
It's awkward to say this, but I'm feeling pretty frustrated.
Seeing Yotaka transform in front of me.
The same thing might happen to Tsubame.
Yogi is probably intending to kill Yotaka.
But I have my reasons not to just stand around and do nothing.
Even though I've cut my ties with them.
They're the ones that I wish would always stay safe and sound.
Gareki.
Once you find an abandoned building,
go and hide yourself there!
You've got to be kidding.
A useless person like me and the one who ruined them should just go die!
The "unnecessary things" that Gareki was talking about... What are they?
Something that has nothing to do with me?
That's not right.
Gareki is going to where Tsubame-chan is.
Even though what's happening to her has nothing to do with him.
Again... I don't remember but people are dead.
I must be sick after all.
If something happened to me, Yotaka would be all alone.
What should I do?
Are you okay?
Don't be afraid.
Um, I...
Tsubame-chan!
Ah.
Blood...
He hasn't completely transformed yet.
Maybe I can still...
Crate of Thorns!
Gather!
Yotaka-kun, listen to me.
I don't wish to fight you.
Please...
For Gareki's sake too.
Okay?
Gareki.
Gare...ki.
Why?
I don't... know.
That man was scary.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You've gotten blood on your hand...
I'm scary too, aren't I?
Hm?
Being near me feels creepy, doesn't it?
No...
What?
You feel warm.
She's so warm... just like Karoku.
Tsubame-chan, you're warm and pretty.
That's why Gareki said...
What?
He wanted you to always be safe and sound.
I've always thought he hated me.
That's not true! Well, ah, um...
Thank you.
Nai-chan, you're kind too.
Isn’t that nice?
Young people really make me smile.
This guy...
He had no intention of killing me.
Why?
Who is this guy?
Yotaka!
Yotaka, you..
What's wrong with you?
What happened...
It's so much more fun to have more people around.
This will bring my research that much closer to completion.
Yogi...
Oh yeah, let's have a party to celebrate our encounter.
Let's have lots of fun!
Tonight's menu will be... this!
Yotaka...
Gareki...
What's up with that look?
What the hell are you doing?
It has nothing to do with you, right?
Those were your words back then...
You...
What are you going to do with Tsubame and your grandfather?
Shut up.
It's too late.
I'll kill you.
You fool.
Wonderful.
Young people are so passionate.
Who the hell are you?
Even if you ask me who I am...
I'm just someone from somewhere.
I like games where I can nurture characters, and I'm playing one right now...
I wanted to retrieve the data on both the twins,
but Yotaka became suspicious of the drug.
He took Tsubame's dosage as well,
so even if Tsubame resonated, she didn't transform.
He even continued to take the drug,
in order to get money for the experiment.
He's so devoted to his family.
Yotaka!
You bastard.
I see... So you're the one...
Tsubaki was also...
Oh yes.
I think she was trying to save her little brother.
When Yotaka transformed for the first time, his power went berserk.
She jumped in, even though she didn't understand what was going on.
And so she...
That's why, I wasn't the one who killed her.
I wanted to make love to her a little more.
You're the one who killed her!
Open your mind and think clearly!
I've seen your face before.
What?
Let me draw flightless wings on your back as well, someday.
Or...
Varuga!
Do you want me to do it now, human?!
I thought you were dead.
How disappointing.
Yotaka, I command you...
to kill everyone here.
No, you mustn't!
Yotaka won't do it!
He won't do such a thing!
I won't do it.
I won't kill.
I refuse to do it!
Oh, I see. So, that's how it is.
So there was a reverse resonance between the two of them, as well.
I've been wondering why he was able to cling onto his last shred of humanity.
I guess that's due to Tsubame pulling him back to his original self.
I see... So this only happens with twins, huh?
Interesting.
But I'm curious, what's so great about living a life of poverty?
"What"?
You don't even know that?
If you can't figure out what it means to laugh and cry each passing day,
then I feel sorry for you.
That’s enough.
I've lost interest.
But I'll tell you something.
You can never return to the past.
You cannot resist your transformation.
Yotaka!
Trying to resist... What a futile effort.
Don't get in the way.
I'm just getting to the best part now.
No!
Gareki...
Kill me.
I don't want to hurt anyone... anymore!
Please, Gareki...
I'm begging you, kill me...
Gareki!
Tsubame...
Yotaka?
Tsubame,
fly somewhere...
far away...
Yotaka!
Be my reason
subete ga ima
全てが今
And now everything
Be my power, future
ugokidasu
動きだす
Begins to move
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
kanjou no namae nante
感情の名前なんて
If we ever talk about what our feelings are...
iidaseba kiri ga nai kedo
言い出せばキリがないけど
There'll be no end to it
kimi no me ga sakebu no nara
キミの目が叫ぶのなら
But for any emotion that your eyes cry out
honnou de kikiwakeru
本能で聞き分ける
I'd instinctively recognize what it is
(Trust)
tsukimatou
つきまとう
I follow you around
(Trash)
soko ni aru
そこにある
It's over there
hikari mo yami mo
光も闇も
Both the light and darkness
tsunagari dasu
繋がりだす
They begin to connect
piisu no you ni
ピースのように
Like puzzle pieces
riyuu ga aru kara
理由があるから
Because there is a reason
guuzen demo nariyuki demo
偶然でも成り行きでも
Whether it happened by chance or by design
shinjitai deai ni kawatteku
信じたい出会いに変わってく
it will change into the encounter that I want to believe in
kokoro no ondo ga
心の温度が
The temperature of my heart
sukoshi zutsu agaru ne
少しずつ上がるね
Rises little by little
misekake ja nai kakehiki mo nai
見せかけじゃない駆け引きもない
I'm not pretending, nor am I bargaining
hontou no jibun no mama de
本当の自分のままで
I'm just being myself
eranda basho ni tatteru koto
選んだ場所に立ってること
I want to tell you
kimi ni tsutaetai yo
キミに伝えたいよ
That I'm standing in the place I've chosen
Be my reason
kimi no soba de
キミの傍で
By your side
Be my power, future
Preview
Smells nice, doesn't it?
Akari
the guest
named
That's a flower.
the guest
named
Akari
is —
Its fragrance smells nice...
the guest
named
written
the guest
named
written
is —
Preview
written
is —
Preview
written
is —
Preview
written
is —
Is it something to eat?
written
this
way
No, it's something to admire.
this
way
written
this
way
Karoku also smells good.
this
way
Preview
this
way
Preview
this
way
Preview
this
way
Preview
this
way
Preview
this
way
Preview
Akari
What?
You smell just like the sun.
Score 6
Wings of Morning Light